WWW.MY-SUBS.COM
(Mobley) He wants to hack Steel
Mountain's climate control system,
raise the facility's heat high
enough to destroy all the tapes.
This is what we're doing.
I'll hit up my Dark Army contact
as soon as you take off.
(Romero) You just gonna hit up the
world's most dangerous hacker crew?
He has my bank account, Ollie.
We cannot just infect Allsafe's network
because of this. I'll lose my job.
Evil Corp's upping their
security protocol.
They are physically copying,
then shipping all
the analog backups.
We go up today.
[speaking Swedish]
I want you to be where
you belong, here with me.
I think I'm happy where I am.
(Shayla) Don't let
me down, okay?
That girl in there is mine.
(Shayla) Did you have something
to do with Vera getting busted?
He's on murder charges.
Do you know that?
It's my plan. I'll go in.
You might be able to
hide it from these nerds,
but I know a junkie
when I see one.
- [sniffles] I'm alone.
- No, you're not.
I'm not going anywhere, kiddo.
[dramatic music]
(Carol) I wish I had better
news for you, Fernando,
but this isn't the
you're-getting-out meeting.
This is only as much
as I could carry.
The D.A. has more.
- How long this gonna be?
- We're talking years.
Yo, you playing?
You get our people out.
That's your use to us.
They have a solid case.
For every charge they're
gonna lay on you,
they have these binders,
your Twitters, your Instagram.
You said they wouldn't
figure this shit out.
(Manny) They can't, brah.
I'm telling you, it
was airtight, V.
Fellas, this isn't
The Imitation Game.
The code here is not
that complicated.
Besides, who told you
to put your business
anywhere near social media?
My aspirational
little brother.
You know how much money
we saved last year?
Made our whole operation
way more efficient.
We were careful.
You tweeted about
every transaction
your business was involved in.
That is the opposite
of careful.
It's no wonder an
anonymous tip turned you in.
- Who called in the tip?
- This is what is meant by anonymous.
It is now spilled milk.
The information got out,
and now they're
coming down hard.
There's no plea on the table.
They're gonna lay
murder one on you.
I ain't pleading anyway.
Men can't sentence me.
That is a cosmic
responsibility.
Someone's gonna get
hurt for this.
That's how we get square
with the universe.
Fernando, we need to
discuss strategy.
- You don't want Supermax.
- Naw, naw.
If they lock me up, the kind of
door they close don't matter.
[ball bouncing]
So that's you.
That's who you are.
- [exhales]
- I know you.
[ball bouncing]
- Synced and corrected by skoad -
www.MY-SUBS.com
- [electronic music]
- Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
[exhales]
Excuse me.
Pardon me. Pardon me.
I already paid.
Just want to pay my respects.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ooh, I'm sorry, man. Sorry.
Just want to pay
my compliments.
Hey, excellent coffee,
fantastic service.
Buy yourself something nice.
♪ ♪
_
(Elliot) Steel Mountain.
We're trying to penetrate
a data security facility
whose tagline literally is...
Nothing is actually
impenetrable.
A place like this says
it is, and it's close,
but people still
built this place.
And if you can hack
the right person,
all of a sudden,
you have a piece of
powerful malware.
People always make
the best exploits.
I've never found it
hard to hack most people.
If you listen to
them, watch them,
their vulnerabilities are like
a neon sign screwed
into their heads.
Mobley's a glutton.
He lacks discipline
from his urges.
I don't want to get
bugs. They spread disease.
(Elliot) Romero is a know-it-all
and a hypochondriac.
(Mobley) Bill Harper
is our first exploit.
He isn't gonna give the
search much scrutiny.
He'll get us to Level 1,
but Bill is not gonna be
able to get us to Level 2.
And we need to get to Level 2.
You're gonna ask to speak
to his supervisor, Wendy.
She'll get us to exactly
where we need to be.
Then we'll be able to get
rid of her from the van.
After that, you connect
the Raspberry Pi
to the climate control
system, and Bob's your uncle.
Now we can hear you,
and you can hear us.
(Elliot) Mr. Robot?
His flaw is he's
absolutely insane.
We're talking clinical.
When they say, "If your friends
jump off a bridge, would you?"
he would, without hesitation,
just to prove something.
He goes in there, he's liable
to blow the whole place up,
just like he wanted to
in the first place.
Sure you don't want
to look over the info
- and the map again?
- I got it.
Okay, James Bond, let's
go mess their shit up.
Boom, boom.
(Elliot) Yes, I also
have security flaws.
I don't like being outside.
I liked morphine too much.
Mr. Sepiol?
(Elliot) I'm talking
to you right now,
and you don't exist.
Sam Sepiol?
Sir?
That's you, Elliot.
Okay.
So sorry you had to wait.
As you can see, there's
always a lot of bustle here.
How can I help you today?
(Mr. Robot) You need a
tour. Don't elaborate.
Um... a tour.
Okay.
I'm sure they told
you at reception
that we... we require
appointments for tours.
My supervisor gives us
all a hard time about that.
I'm Sam Sepiol.
You should look me up.
Okay.
[clears throat]
A little inelegant,
but we can work with it.
Tell you what.
Have your company call
over to new accounts,
and we can set something
up later this week.
Ask for Bill Harper.
They'll know where to find me.
[chuckles]
(Mr. Robot) Listen, Bill.
You think your boss
gives you a hard time now?
You're gonna get a
really hard time
right after I
walk out of here.
I'm not rescheduling, Bill.
When I walk out that door,
I'm never coming back.
That's your ass, Bill.
I really think you
should look me up.
It... it just doesn't
work like that.
I'm sorry, sir.
You take care, okay?
I'm coming out.
It's not working.
(Mr. Robot) It's gonna work.
Hang in there.
I was being too weird.
(Mr. Robot) Just like every
other tech billionaire.
Slow your roll.
It's gonna happen.
(Elliot) It's no wonder
Wikipedia is never accurate.
Anyone can edit them.
Well, not anyone.
Nerds like Mobley built a
lot of credit over the years
with his 20,000 edits.
And still people trust it,
beholden to all the Mobleys of
the world for their information.
Mr. Sepiol?
Mr. Sepiol!
I have some good news.
[chuckles]
(Ollie) Stop it. Stop it.
Can you stop packing
for, like, five minutes?
Can we just hash this
out like adults?
I love you.
You don't even know
why you're crying.
Let's get married.
Ollie, will you please stop?
Angela... Angela, you can't
just give up on us like this.
[scoffs]
I mean, have you even
thought this through?
What are you gonna do, go
live with your dad in Jersey?
Come on.
- You're ruining your life.
- Maybe, but I also ruined yours.
Why do you have my work ID?
Did you...
did you... do you... do you...
do you know what's
gonna happen?
There will be fallout from this,
and I'm gonna tell them...
I used your computer, so
tell them whatever you want.
Are you serious?
Did you even think about
how this would affect me?
I did.
(Bill) Here's an idea
of how big this place is.
We have our own fire department,
inside the building,
just for us.
And you can't have a fire
department without a fire truck,
and you can't have a
fire truck without roads.
We have all of that, inside.
Imagine that.
♪ ♪
(Mr. Robot) Elliot, now's
the time we get rid of Bill.
[elevator bell dings]
There's so much information...
(Mr. Robot) Okay, we're gonna
need to roll up our sleeves here.
You have to destroy Bill in
order to get to a supervisor.
There's one vault in here
that's 200,000 square feet.
That's the size of
a shopping mall,
and that's just one.
- Bill, where are those giant vaults?
- Oh, they're on Level 2,
but that's not
part of the tour.
Even I don't have
authorization.
(Mr. Robot) He's not gonna
take you for ice cream.
He has to go away.
There's no place in
this plan for Bill.
Now, right down here...
Everything okay, sir?
(Mr. Robot) We need to tear
Bill down piece by piece.
You need to wipe that smile
off of his stupid face.
Sir, are you okay?
You're not... you're
not saying anything.
(Mr. Robot) Dig
into him, Elliot.
You of all people can
do this, Elliot.
You know how it feels when
someone makes you small.
You understand what
happens when someone exposes
the thing you fear
most about yourself.
(Elliot's mother) Answer me!
Answer me!
[Elliot grunts]
Get up.
Just get up!
I hate you.
You're nothing.
You're worthless.
Think about it, Bill.
Think about what?
If you died,
would anyone care?
Would they really care?
Yeah, maybe they'd
cry for a day,
but let's be honest.
No one would give a shit.
They wouldn't.
The few people that would feel
obligated to go to your funeral
would probably be annoyed
and leave as early
as possible.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
That's who you are.
That's what you are.
You're nothing to anyone,
to everyone.
Think about it, Bill.
'Cause if you do,
if you let yourself...
You'll know I'm telling
you the truth.
So instead of wasting
any more of my time,
I need you to go call
someone that matters,
because, Bill...
You don't.
I'll...
[sniffles]
I'll call my supervisor.
(Elliot) And that's why Bill
Harper is a perfect exploit,
desperate enough for the
business to break protocol
and let me in.
Lonely enough to break.
I need a supervisor in L1S3.
(man) Copy that.
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter]
(Mr. Robot) Don't apologize.
You're almost there.
You did great.
(Romero) Once Wendy gets
there, we'll send her a text
letting her know her
pregnant wife is in labor.
Once she leaves, that
should give you enough time
to plant the Pi, you dig?
[door closes]
Trudy Davis,
Accounts Supervisor.
Is there a problem here?
- Mr. Sepiol is asking...
- Trudy?
- What the fuck? - for
someone more senior than me.
I don't seem to
have your name.
I'm Sam Sepiol?
- Is that a question?
- Trudy? Trudy?
(Mobley) Where's Wendy?
We only prepped for Wendy.
Where the hell is Wendy?
I need Wendy, actually.
And how do you know Wendy?
She didn't come in today.
_
(Trudy) What is it that
you need, Mr. Sepiol?
Um...
I would love a
tour of Level 2.
I don't know what
you've been told,
but we don't allow that.
I'll see you out.
You can go, Bill.
Follow me to the lobby.
(Romero) This woman's a ghost.
None of these are her.
No Facebook, no LinkedIn.
She's been married
for 30 years.
All we have is her
husband's cell phone number.
He doesn't even have
a picture online.
No hobbies, no kids,
no credit problems,
no weird sex stuff.
House paid off.
(Mobley) I need... I need
to... I need to think.
[quietly] The
elevator's almost here.
Yes, that's how they work
when you press the button.
Okay.
People... people are
all just people, right?
When it gets down to
it, everyone's the same.
They love something.
They want something.
They fear something.
Specifics help, but
specifics don't change
the way that everyone
is vulnerable.
It just changes the way that we
access those vulnerabilities.
_
[phone vibrates]
[elevator bell dings]
I-I have to go. I'm sorry.
I need to go to my office.
Reception will see you out.
What'd you do?
(Mobley) I spoofed a
text from her husband.
_
It's a palm print scanner.
(Mr. Robot) Get out of there.
(Romero) There's one
door manually locked.
It's a fire code thing,
and I think you can pick it.
- Where?
- It's at the end of the hallway
if you're heading north on L1.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
The stairs don't
go to Level 2.
They go to a parking lot.
(Romero) You're on the complete
wrong side of the building.
You're gonna have to double
back and go through the door
you came in and
make a run for it.
Elliot...
I thought I saw you.
What are you doing here?
Thank you. Y'all come
back to Wingstravaganza.
- Okay, real important...
- Mm-hmm.
Wingstravaganza means
wings and extravaganza.
- Do you know what extravaganza means?
- Yep, it's a big deal.
- You got it.
- Mm-hmm.
You look nervous.
Are you excited?
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
So you'll shadow me for the
week, but don't sweat it.
It's like every
other server job.
Well, I've actually never
been a waitress before.
Oh.
This is kind of like
a new beginning for me.
- What were you doing before?
- Pharmaceutical sales.
Fancy.
You must have made bank.
- What happened?
- Oh, um, just, you know, Obamacare.
Welcome to Steel
Mountain's data center.
Our facility meets
diamond specifications
and features a tier 10
certified build and design,
providing you with a
safe, rock-solid fortress
for your data needs.
All of our
facilities implement
comprehensive
security measures...
(Tyrell) They say I'm overdoing
it, and I say exactly.
[laughs] So yeah.
Elliot.
- Nice meeting you.
- You too.
- Tell your wife I said hi.
- I will.
Those men I just
shook hands with,
financiers of
Hezbollah and ISIS.
I wouldn't stare.
(Elliot) Did he know
I was gonna be here?
Does he know why I'm here?
Shit, he's gonna kill me.
- As you were saying?
- Uh, just a routine data process check.
Allsafe does them
all the time.
But why would they send you?
That type of thing
isn't usually handled
by the engineers, is it?
We've been overlapping
a lot in our duties.
Budget reasons.
It seems we both had the
idea to work off-site today.
Let's call this fortuitous.
- Join me for lunch?
- S-sure.
- I eat lunch.
- [laughs]
So you are like
the rest of us.
Come.
He got owned, man.
We got to go.
We're not going anywhere.
This changes nothing.
What can I get you, Elliot?
Have a lot of things here.
(Mr. Robot) He has
a vulnerability.
He's an arrogant prick,
and he's proud of it.
He cares what you
think about him,
even though he probably
hates that he does.
Tyrell Wellick's greatest
asset is his hubris,
but it's also his flaw,
and that's your exploit.
Would be nice.
You eat here?
This place?
(Romero) Is that your
plan, to piss him off?
No, wait, man. Wait.
_
[snaps fingers]
(Mr. Robot cutting out)
Now remember, Elliot,
you'll lose our
signal on Level 2.
Elliot.
Elliot, say something
if you can hear us.
I'm impressed you came
all the way out here.
Allsafe is finished,
but you won't let it die.
We're the same.
We're perfectionists.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I've seen our waiter
here for the last...
seven years.
Must be in his 50s,
maybe has kids,
divorced, second
wife, more kids,
and I wonder,
what must he think of himself?
His life's potential reached
at a 30 grand a year salary,
an economy car he
still owes money on,
two-bedroom apartment,
child support, coupons.
I couldn't bear it,
a life like that.
The life of an
ordinary cockroach
whose biggest value
is to serve me salad.
♪ ♪
[radio chatter]
[handcuffs clink]
[radio chatter continues]
[pen writing on paper]
I have to go to the bathroom.
♪ ♪
(Elliot) Goddamn
withdrawals again.
Or is it Tyrell Wellick?
Is he toying with me?
What kind of game
are we playing?
Am I his malware?
♪ ♪
I had to wash my face.
Hard to breathe...
here.
I know you framed Terry Colby.
I-I didn't.
Your father worked at
Evil Corp before he died.
That's a matter
of public record.
[urinal flushes]
[water running]
I'm not turning you in, if
that's what you're thinking.
I don't even have proof,
and even if I did,
I don't care.
Just wanted to know
your weakness.
Now I do.
Revenge.
How ordinary.
Just like our waiter.
But even extraordinary people,
and I believe you are,
are driven by
human banalities.
And unfortunately,
we're all human.
Except me, of course.
I'm joking, Elliot.
Enjoy your long
drive back home.
I'm having a helicopter
take me back to New York.
You take care, Elliot.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[exhales deeply]
♪ ♪
_
No. Bullshit.
Dude, bullshit!
- What did they say?
- Oh, I don't know.
Basically that they're a
bunch of dickless assholes.
- Where are you going?
- To fix it.
No one else is going to.
Darlene, wait.
I really don't think you
should keep pushing them.
Put it this way.
Either I'm fixing
this or breaking it.
Their call.
Hi, Pumpkin.
Hey, Daddy.
- Why aren't you at work?
- I broke up with Ollie.
I know.
Just got off the
phone with him.
Come on.
He was sobbing.
He wanted me to tell
you something like,
"I'll always love you.
Please come back."
- Oh, and he can learn to forgive you.
- [Angela chuckles]
Jesus.
- What did you say?
- I told him I thought you
should've broken up with him a
long time ago and hung up on him.
Nice.
- What did he mean, anyway?
- Just normal work and...
money stuff.
And, well, he cheated on me,
so there's that.
Well, the cheating part,
I'm not surprised.
Not trying to make you feel
bad, honey, but come on.
The kid's a douchebag.
- As for the money...
- Dad, no.
I'll float you some money
for professional development.
- Dad...
- Call it a loan,
but do not pay me back.
And you'll stay
here and commute
until you can save
for an apartment.
I can't make you
do any of that.
And you didn't.
It's what I want.
- Are you hungry?
- Yeah.
No, no. Sit, sit, sit, sit.
Relax.
- What would you like?
- You don't need to cook for me, Dad.
French toast coming up!
[horns honk in the distance]
[speaking Swedish]
[classical music]
- Mm-hmm.
- Ah.
[speaking Swedish]
Mm.
[scoffs]
- Why are they backing out?
- [sighs]
This is a library.
You want to discuss that,
go back to the IRC island.
They banned me
from the channel!
What happened?
We just owned Steel Mountain.
We did our part, and
it went perfect.
Come on, we both know that
shit didn't go perfect.
Well, it doesn't matter!
They called it off.
We pulled our side together,
and your side called it
off like it was nothing.
You got your answer.
You better tell your pal
whiterose to stop being a pussy
and start growing a pair
because we don't have time
to dilly-dally around...
And now you're gonna talk
about this in the world?
Do you even care
who hears you?
Face it, Darlene.
It's over.
Walk away.
I can't go back to
my people with that.
Tell me why.
You said the Dark Army
was with us on this.
[sighs]
- Between us?
- I'm not about to goddamn tweet about it.
They were out before you
ever got to Steel Mountain.
I don't know why. That's
all they said to me.
I know you had your heart set,
but for real this time,
just let it go.
[screams]
- I need seats mostly.
- No.
I imagine it must be exciting
to work in government.
- It's like a spy movie.
- [laughs]
- Can you read my secret emails?
- Mm, no.
My job is mostly paperwork
and bureaucracy.
They always want more
than the technology allows.
I don't even have time to
read your secret emails.
But it's a stopgap for me.
I'm restless.
I'm always itching
for something else.
There have been a lot
of something elses.
[laughter]
For both of us.
[chuckles]
Before this, I
worked at an NGO,
and before that, I worked
at Microsoft for a year,
which felt like a decade.
[laughter]
Your place is beautiful.
I wish I could take
the compliment.
The decorating is
Scott's domain.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- Very nice.
- Yeah.
- Where's all the... the antiques from?
- They're...
So they tapped you
for CTO, yes?
They're 17th century.
Don't be surprised.
Suspicious is more accurate.
I was beginning to wonder
why you set this dinner.
Four people in the world
know about my conversations.
Somehow you're number five.
Then I'm exactly what
you need in a right hand.
So that's what this is about.
Isn't everything
about something?
Like, we were thinking
about, is it is it babyproof?
Ah, yeah, that's...
that's a consideration.
If you were me,
- would you trust you as your right hand?
- If I were you,
I wouldn't have even
let me in the house.
[chuckles]
(Joanna) We finished
everything upstairs...
[phone vibrating]
Hey.
Hey, it's me.
- Is now a good time?
- Yeah.
I'm at my new job.
- How's it going?
- [sighs] Seriously, it's hard as hell,
but I am getting
the hang of it.
At first, it took me, like,
years to marry ketchups,
but it turns out I'm amazing
at upselling
expensive cocktails.
I'm not surprised.
And then when I have to
put together to go orders,
it's like bagging Molly, so
I'm, like, kind of an expert.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
Wow, I've never heard you say
a sentence like
that before, ever.
I did what I had to do today.
Well, if you're
around tonight,
come over and tell
me about it, okay?
I got to go.
Okay, bye.
You seem to know how
to drink your wine.
[big band music playing]
I indulge in few things,
but I do love wine.
- Yourself?
- In my other life,
when I could drink for one.
But even then I
had cheap tastes.
It's safe to smell, though.
Put your nose in there.
♪ Mean a thing to me ♪
You know, to me, it
smells like every wine.
[chuckles]
- But I'd love to learn.
- Uh-huh.
Dried red fruit, fresh violet,
uh, lemon peel.
Try it again.
Smell and really...
really think about it.
Mmm, I do smell lemon.
- Sharon?
- Yeah?
How do you not blow your brains
out being married to him?
Smell again.
Excuse me?
- Shall I repeat the question?
- You're a guest in our house.
- A very honest one.
- [laughs]
Wow.
[sets glass down]
I think I'll mistake what you
said as a joke in poor taste
and excuse myself
to the bathroom.
I have a beautiful
vintage over here.
I would love to just
show you the label.
♪ Just a tragic picture show ♪
(Scott) Let's see here.
Nope.
There's the one.
This is my prized
possession, actually.
Take a look at this.
♪ I'm begging you ♪
[door opens]
I'm in here.
Can I help you?
Thank you for a
lovely evening.
[sighs]
- Siege in Stormstout!
- Carcass Emblem!
[laughter]
We got problems.
- Is the Pi online?
- Yeah, we're in the whole system.
We could deliver the whole
payload right now if we wanted.
And yet I hear no applause.
Applaud.
[chuckles]
You have to tell them.
- What?
- We lost China.
- I'm sorry?
- The Dark Army is bailing.
- Why?
- They don't answer whys apparently.
That's no problem.
We'll just call 'em back.
- We'll set up another meet ASAP...
- Dude, did you not hear me?
They've gone dark.
It's not happening.
I know. I know.
I get it, okay? I fucked up.
[phone vibrating]
[phone stops vibrating]
Let's not wait, then.
Let's do it anyway, just us.
Let's do it right now.
Okay? We execute now.
We execute on our side and
trust that the Dark Army
gets their shit
together and follows.
Why do they get
to dictate terms?
We dictate terms!
- [shushing]
- We can go now.
If we move forward
and they don't,
China still holds all
the redundant information.
It will be pointless.
And if we wait, it'll
also be pointless.
Everything you guys did
today would be for nothing.
- [grunts]
- God, are you crazy?
It will have no effect!
It'll take down their
network for weeks.
They'll recover.
It would still hurt them.
We don't want to hurt them!
We want to kill them!
And neither will happen
if we do nothing right now.
- What are you doing, huh?
- Take another step, and I'll do it.
Think about what
you're doing, okay?
All right?
In a month, they're gonna
be up and running again
with even better security.
We are not gonna get
another shot at this.
The revolution that
we've always talked about
will be gone,
dead, and buried.
We will have failed
because of you.
Please do not do this.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[scoffs]
Is there anyone here
who can communicate
with this woman?
♪ ♪
[whispers] Please.
Tell me it's okay to execute.
♪ ♪
But we were so close.
It's not over.
We'll rework it.
We'll figure something out.
We got this far.
We'll find a way,
just not tonight.
[sighs]
[door opens and closes]
This is all my fault.
[sighs]
Come on.
You can crash at my place.
[crying]
[electronic music]
(Elliot) My father picked
me up from school one day,
and we played hooky and
went to the beach.
It was too cold to
go in the water,
so we sat on a blanket
and ate pizza.
When I got home, my
sneakers were full of sand,
and I dumped it on
my bedroom floor.
I didn't know the difference.
I was six.
My mother screamed
at me for the mess,
but he wasn't mad.
He said that billions
of years ago,
the world shifting and
the oceans moving
brought that sand to
that spot on the beach,
and then I took it away.
"Every day," he said,
"we change the world,"
which is a nice thought
until I think about how
many days and lifetimes
I would need to bring
a shoe full of sand home
until there is no beach,
until it made a
difference to anyone.
Every day, we
change the world,
but to change the world in
a way that means anything,
that takes more time
than most people have.
It never happens all at once.
It's slow.
It's methodical.
It's exhausting.
We don't all have
the stomach for it.
♪ ♪
- Hey, sweetie.
- I'm gonna go for a run.
Nice.
[dog barking]
Shayla's got the dog.
She doesn't shit
on her pillows.
- That's a plus, I guess.
- [phone beeping]
[dog continues barking]
[phone continues beeping]
- Shayla?
- (Vera) Hey, brah.
Sometimes the universe
aligns perfectly.
Here I am, locked away.
Still, it brings
you right to me.
[Angela panting]
♪ ♪
- Synced and corrected by
skoad - www.MY-SUBS.com