Are you wet?
Aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Hold on.
I can't now.
I can't get up now.
Why not?
He's up.
He'll go down soon.
When?
Soon.
He goes down that soon?
Yes, give it a minute.
Do you do drugs?
It's time to go.
Shall we?
Hi, Teacher!
To do or not to do
Let me introduce students...
No, soon-to-be teachers.
We're very excited
to be here.
And to be learning
from you all.
Where's LEE Yu-lim's desk?
That asshole...
What?
I told him to wait
to meet the student teachers.
He said he was too tired
and left.
I bet he's sleeping
in his car.
He drank a lot last night.
Get the picture?
How old are you?
- Born in 78?
- Yes.
You went back to school?
I went to another college.
What was your major?
Art.
Art...
- Why do you wanna do this?
- Sorry?
I mean teach.
Well, it's a stable career.
But it's no fun.
Teaching is no fun.
Okay.
Watch out for the VP.
He's very anal.
It won't be easy at first.
It's a lot of politics.
Flattery isn't all it takes.
They smile to your face,
but talk dirty behind your back.
You should know
when to push and tell.
Okay.
No questions?
Today is the first day,
and I'm kind of lost.
How old are you, LEE?
Umm...
I'm 26.
So I'm a year younger.
Isn't she the student teacher
for your class?
Wow, she looks so different.
Quite pretty and elegant.
Where to?
Hi.
Hop in.
No, it's okay.
It's hard to get a cab here.
Get in.
Come drinking with us.
Drinking?
Is it on you?
Sure.
Come on, he's paying.
I have to go.
A boyfriend driving a Mercedes?
He must be loaded.
What does she think she is,
driving such a car?
It's her boyfriend's.
So you're buying drinks?
I lied.
- No way.
- Give me a cigarette.
It's new on the market.
It looks great on you.
It makes you stand out.
Do you like it?
I don't like it.
I told you
this wasn't my thing.
Why don't you try...
Forget it.
- Good night
- I have surgery tonight.
I won't be reachable
by phone.
Call me.
- Yu-lim.
- What?
You're different tonight.
What?
I'm loving it.
Yeah, me too.
We provide ideal circumstances
for studying
with the best facilities
in the country.
We rear those who will lead...
We always go to SokCho
for school fieldtrips.
Why not Jeju Island?
It was your boyfriend,
wasn't it?
Yes.
He must be rich.
We're going out tonight.
Pay your dues.
- How much?
- $30
And $10 for her.
So it's $40 for both of you.
I have no cash on me.
You pay for me.
I'll pay you back later.
- I'm broke too.
- Come on, don't be cheap.
You always do this.
You're really broke?
- I'll pay you back!
- Here.
You don't carry a wallet
on purpose, or what?
I was gonna
go to the bank later.
Why don't you sing?
- You go ahead.
- Come on.
Please.
I go first?
Okay.
Hey, why'd you stop?
This is no fun.
Let's go somewhere else.
I have to go.
I think of us as partners.
I don't care about others.
But between you and me,
there should be a partnership.
What do you think?
I agree.
- You sure?
- Yes.
You're not just saying that,
are you?
No.
Tonight, we should be doing
a lot of talking.
I wanted to talk a lot too.
But something came up
at home.
If that's the case...
- I'm really sorry.
- It's okay.
Bye.
Wait.
Will it take long?
I don't know.
I should go and see.
Here's what.
Can you make it back
when you're done?
I'll call you.
We won't be done before 12.
Give me a call.
Okay.
Not offended, right?
Right.
You can come now.
Nobody's going home
until you get here.
- Don't overdo it.
- We'll be waiting, CHOI.
Hello?
Okay, hold on.
He says the surgery won't be over
until morning.
Thanks.
They all left?
Yeah.
They were too wasted.
I called you so many times.
You didn't answer.
It was out of battery.
Okay then.
Why don't we drink
and talk?
Don't you have any other
love stories to share?
A heart-breaking one.
No.
You must like clams.
Yes.
You guys have sex,
don't you?
Every couple does, don't they?
What about you?
It's been about 2 months.
After 6 years of dating,
you kind of lose interest.
6 years?
Do you love her?
Sure.
She's more like a sister now.
I see.
What does she do?
The same thing I do.
Which school?
At MyungShin High.
MyungShin High?
A friend of mine works there.
What's her name?
I'll tell you later.
It's okay.
Excuse me.
You have beautiful legs.
Thanks.
You're eating a lot of clams.
Have some.
I feel like
a different kind of clam.
- CHOI.
- Yes?
I don't know if I should be
saying this, but...
I wanna sleep with you.
Let's do it.
Stop it, LEE.
I wanna hold you.
I think you're drunk.
Let's go.
I'm very straightforward.
Isn't it better
than being a pervert?
You do this to every girl
you meet?
No way.
Only when I like her.
You like me?
Yes.
But we just met.
At first sight,
I knew I liked you.
Have you had sex
with a total stranger?
Sure.
There are girls like that?
Of course.
They're so many.
How's that possible?
What?
Having sex without love?
Why are you laughing?
You're like a kid.
Come on, you're not 16.
Love is good
for the first 3 months.
Exhilarating?
Electric?
According to this research,
there's this hormone
that gives such feelings
And it lasts for 3 months.
Isn't it 3 years?
I heard it was 3 years.
It's 3 months.
So if you feel like it,
just do it.
Love is a funny thing.
It doesn't exit.
If you see someone you like,
sleep with him.
No strings.
Be cool about it.
Sorry.
I don't feel like it.
Wait.
Why don't we kiss over there?
Hold on.
LEE, you're putting us
in an awkward situation.
What did I do?
All I wanted was sex.
It might make things
easier for us.
So many motels around here.
You live in Hapjung, right?
Yes.
- Hapjung!
- Sorry.
Wait!
Hapjung!
Did you see that new teacher?
Yeah, she's a fox!
She worked at Il-sin High before.
She had an affair
with a married teacher.
Word got out
and she got fired.
- What a slut!
- Tell me about it.
Should I hit on her?
She might fall for me.
Dream on!
Let's go sit.
Hi.
So you guys watch it.
This field is very conservative.
Once you mess up
like that,
you're branded for life.
Got home okay last night?
Yes.
Over here, CHOI.
Hi.
I'll eat here.
Eat with me.
I'll eat with them.
I don't wanna eat alone.
Come on.
Slept well?
No.
Why not?
I have insomnia.
Really?
How many hours of sleep a day?
I rarely sleep.
Excuse me.
You hardly touched anything.
I've lost my appetite.
Enjoy your lunch.
Wait.
I don't feel like eating either.
Let's go have some coffee.
Let's go.
Try to get some sleep.
Go to bed.
Why can't you sleep?
Let me help you.
Sleep some.
Insomnia?
We're not here to party,
but to learn.
Before checking in for the night,
we'll run a check
on your belongings.
Teachers, do it thoroughly.
They brought everything.
That Hennessy is mine.
No way.
We'll share it.
Founders keepers!
Whom should we drink with?
Count the PE teacher out.
Let me hear it!
It doesn't matter who wins.
Under the feet!
Make it louder, guys!
Louder!
Hey.
Get over here.
KIM!
You can sing
your throat out later.
Why isn't she answering?
It's an alarm.
I thought you had insomnia.
Somebody else set it,
but I don't know how to undo it.
Let me do it for you.
It's weird.
What's wrong with it?
Phonebook
Deleting
This isn't right.
What?
All numbers deleted
Where'd you buy it?
You need to have it fixed.
Wait.
We need to talk.
About what?
You misunderstand.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I'm sorry.
Give me a break, will you?
I'll fix it.
Forget it.
Don't be mad.
I can't bear the guilt.
Okay.
Smile for me.
Go ahead.
Come on.
There you go.
Come on, come on.
Please, stop it.
Why?
This is wrong.
Come on.
I'll keep him in
for 5 seconds.
Are you nuts?
5 seconds!
Stop it!
You okay?
- Get off me.
- Wait, CHOI.
CHOI?
CHOI!
Can I see you later?
We need to talk.
Who is it?
It's Hye-won.
My counselor's girlfriend
works at her school.
Really?
They've been together
for 6 years.
They're getting married soon.
Is he nice to you?
No, not at all.
He's mean
and a pain in the neck.
No chemistry at all.
Should we order more?
I'm full, though.
She's ignoring my messages.
- Hi.
- Come on in.
Here you go.
You didn't have to do this.
Oh, it's caviar.
- I know you like it.
- You're so sweet.
What'd he get you?
He never buys me anything
from school fieldtrips.
I gave him whatever he wanted,
raising him without his dad.
So he doesn't know
how to give back.
Don't raise your kids
like that.
Why do you come over
so often?
You would ask me to come
and help your mom.
Forget it.
Good morning!
Did you...
This is good.
I've never thought of this.
I'm learning a lot
from you too.
Very nice.
Here.
Can I go now?
Meet me out back
in an hour.
Excuse me.
How about bean curd soup?
I know this place.
It's really good.
You know I hate it.
Come on, you'll like it.
That place was even on TV.
It's homemade style!
Let's eat something else.
CHOI, what do you feel like?
You can decide for us.
Bean curd soup sounds good.
I can't believe
how delicious this is.
Not good?
It's good.
You don't like it?
Should I?
Thanks.
It's a great day
for a car wash.
What's the point?
It's a jalopy.
- Coffee.
- Thanks.
- Go ahead.
- No, I'm okay.
Excuse me?
LEE?
What?
Can I see the final papers
from last semester?
Can we talk for a minute?
Anything bothering you?
No.
You hardly ate earlier.
Aren't you hungry?
I am.
Wanna go to the cafeteria
with me?
No. Better yet...
You got aspirin?
I have a terrible headache.
Let me go get some.
Wait.
Oh God...
What's wrong with me?
Come here, will you?
Come on, closer.
My head hurts so much.
Can I lean on you?
Much better.
So nice.
Your girlfriend
at MyungShin High...
It's KIM Hui-jung, isn't it?
How'd you know?
I told you my friend works there.
- Did you Tell her?
- What?
- That I'm hitting on you.
- Yes.
What?
I shouldn't have?
You really did?
Yes.
What'd you tell her?
- About you.
- What about me?
Everything.
What, you feel guilty?
Look, CHOI.
It's a private matter
between us.
How could you?
Unless you're crazy...
How could a reasonable being
do such a thing?
Are you insane?
Let's talk outside.
Teachers in general are
very stern and conservative.
Since you're new and green,
I just wanted to help you
adapt better.
I haven't pulled hierarchy shit
on you, have I?
You think this is funny?
Who do you think you are?
You can't survive here
with that attitude.
Never seen a student teacher
like you.
I've been so nice to you,
and you disdain me?
Then stop bothering me.
CHOI,
I think you are totally mistaken.
- I wasn't...
- I'm warning you.
Don't you touch me again.
CHOI...
You hate me that much?
I really liked you.
Wanna sleep with me?
Yes.
What?
It's $500.
What is?
It will cost you $500
to sleep with me.
Are you nuts?
I never do it for nothing.
What are you, a hooker?
Isn't it better?
There's no love between us.
So why do it?
What's wrong with you?
Come to your senses!
Then forget it.
There's motel out there.
Let's go somewhere quiet
and talk.
Talk.
Not here.
I didn't hit on you
just for sex.
I don't want to any more.
I'm doing this
only because I like you.
Why can't you see that?
Motel
If you have nothing to say,
let's go.
Come up here please.
No thanks.
I'm so tired.
Why don't we...
Wait.
Come here for a second.
Just for a second.
Come here.
You taste so good.
What are you doing?
You want $500?
I'll give you $500.
You're so wet.
If you wanna do it, do it right.
You wanted to do me
at first sight, didn't you?
You're so good.
You too.
I can't believe your boyfriend
doesn't do you every night.
What a waste?
I don't like sex.
You do.
I don't.
Yes, you do.
Missed calls? Hui-jung
Hey, what's up?
Where were you?
You didn't answer your phone.
Oh... we had a meeting.
A long one.
Yeah, really?
Yeah
- Getting off early?
- Yeah.
Let's go eat steamed Angler
for dinner.
You like it, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
But I don't feel good today.
- You don't?
- No.
Listen.
I'm kind of busy now.
I'll call you back.
Okay.
Did you talk to her?
What?
Wasn't it Hui-jung?
Yes.
How'd you know?
She called many times earlier.
So...?
You left with that student teacher.
So I told her
you guys went for lunch.
God damn it!
What?
Why the fuck did you
tell her that?
Watch your mouth, kid.
Jesus fucking Christ!
What the...
This is really good.
Eat some.
Yeah, I am.
You feel better now?
Yeah, this helps.
You know spicy food is
good for colds.
Where were you?
It's late.
Why didn't you call me?
I did.
You didn't answer it.
I didn't know.
Your cousin's fiancé
studied economics abroad.
Here.
They bragged so much.
So your dad told them
you were dating a doctor.
It's the whole competition thing.
Why? Oh dad...
It's not like
we're getting married.
You've met his parents.
It's a done deal.
How's he doing?
Not good.
The economy is so down.
KIM Yeon-ho
Leave a message after...
Here's an important notice.
Our school has a problem
with recycling.
Since last spring...
I called you a few times
last night.
It was out of battery.
Are you free tonight?
No, I'm busy.
I know this new raw fish restaurant.
Delicious and cheap.
Can I see you
after the meeting?
Why?
We need to talk.
About what?
You're scaring me.
This is very important
for me.
Be honest with me.
Okay.
You swear?
I do.
On your parents' names?
Okay.
Are you getting married
next month?
Yes.
I am.
Good for you.
I'm gonna go.
Wait!
I'll forget the whole thing.
Buy me raw fish.
I'm busy with
wedding arrangements.
You're really something.
I feel like I've been used.
You don't mind hurting others.
But you're so self-protective.
I've been truthful
with my feelings all along.
That is exactly why.
That's why
I'm hurting so much now!
You don't like it?
I do.
Why aren't you eating then?
Can we move to the room?
Why?
Let's move to the room.
Excuse me?
You don't like it crowded?
No.
My hands become so shaky
that I can't even eat.
Same for me.
Let me tell you.
I can't even fly.
Like it's gonna kill me.
That's the case
when I'm on the subway.
Should we visit
the nuthouse together?
Can we?
I've always wanted to.
But I thought I'd really go crazy
if I went alone.
I don't trust a guy who says,
"I love you. "
Why not?
I had this friend in college.
She fell in love
with the assistant professor.
He was handsome, attractive...
and married.
And you know what was worse?
She wasn't the only student
he was seeing.
And he took money from her
and other girls.
It's a typical story.
Right.
Isn't it?
She was so stupid
to fall for a guy like that.
Then he made up stories
that made her look like a psycho.
So she had to drop out.
Why did he?
Because she wouldn't let him
get away with it.
Still, how could he do that?
He once liked her.
If you're married
and date your student,
they won't give you tenure
due to the moral issues.
So he made up stories
that my friend had seduced her
and stalked him around.
What a dick.
What happened to her?
She's dead.
She jumped
off a building.
She killed herself over a guy?
I don't think
you know girls well.
I don't understand.
I feel sorry for her.
She was deceived by a dick
and killed herself for that?
I bet no guy can deceive you.
You're strong.
Right?
Yeah.
You love him?
No.
I don't love anybody.
Why marry him then?
He's stable, successful,
and nice to me.
That's what matters.
So go back to your girlfriend.
What we're doing...
It's nothing but a fling,
and won't last for long.
You know that, don't you?
Hello?
Checking out?
God!
Where am I?
What happened?
Did you rape me?
What are you talking about?
We agreed to call it quits.
Don't put this on me.
I have no idea
how we ended up here.
Where's my underwear?
A lot of motels here.
You can come back later
with your boyfriend.
Is there a motel
that you guys patronize?
We don't go to one.
You do it at home?
He's never been to my place.
Really?
For 3 years?
Yes.
Why not?
I never bring guys home.
You're strange.
Then where do you do it?
I hear some give you points
like frequent flyer.
Stay 10 nights and get 1 free
You often go to a motel?
No,
it's been a few years.
Why?
I want to,
but she hates it.
Why?
She hates using sheets
somebody else has used.
She's anal in that aspect.
Maybe she doesn't like doing it
with you.
Come on, that's not it.
She's not like others.
She's a bit rigid
and doesn't like sex.
Who doesn't like sex?
My girlfriend.
She can't even imagine herself
naked with another guy.
She think it's dirty.
She's coy.
I don't think you know
your girlfriend well enough.
Not everybody is like you.
Some like you are open
about sex.
And others hate it naturally.
Everybody's different.
You officially raped me.
CHOI!
We were hugging in bed.
You call that rape?
It's love!
Ditch him ASAP.
They'll study characteristics of
of different celestial spheres.
In the introductory lesson,
the students will...
We're having a meeting.
Where are you?
And encourage the students
to present about the...
Why aren't you
answering the phone?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Why is your cell phone off?
CHOI, pick up.
I'm worried about you.
Are you sick?
Is that it?
God, this is ridiculous.
Come on, pick up!
This is too much.
You should've called in sick.
You're making me upset.
Personnel Records
How could you do that?
It's a job!
You can't just skip a day
without notice.
This is right.
Is she out?
I see it!
That's your bag, isn't it?
You drank beer alone?
You're so funny.
Damn!
CHOI, I'm cold and hungry.
Are you with him?
Should I report to the principle
that you quit?
Once I do, that's it.
If you get an F for this,
you can't even graduate.
I'll count to three.
If I leave, you're in trouble.
One.
Two.
Three!
I can't believe
I have no mirror in the car.
Damn!
Damn it!
There!
I see you!
CHOI!
You can't hide
under the blanket!
Does your girlfriend know
about this?
No.
Don't you feel guilty?
Why are you saying that?
You don't know?
Look, think about it.
I'm not asking you
to marry me, am I?
We'll just date.
It's no big deal.
We'll spend time together
and have fun.
Get permission from her then.
How can I?
She will pull my hair out
once she finds out.
That's what I am saying.
You need to stop this.
I don't wanna do this either.
But I can't help it.
Let it go.
Don't do this.
Or give me a grace period.
What?
Time to forget you.
I can't live like this.
I can't do anything.
Until the first snowfall.
It's only a few months away.
How about it?
Then you don't have
to break up with him.
I'll try to forget you.
I promise.
I won't bother you then.
Then...
What if I do by then?
What?
What if I bother you?
What then?
Any plan for that?
If so...
I'll give you a grace period.
Like until the spring.
Forget it.
Come on!
You don't want me
to make a scene, do you?
What is this?
You told me to wait here
and took a shower?
Your hair is wet!
Do you know how long I waited?
Let's go.
Where?
To talk.
Let's go to your place.
No way.
Let's go to a cafe.
My legs hurt.
Hey!
Nice.
Bigger than my room.
Get out of here now.
Are you out of your mind?
Wait,
you cleaned too?
While I was waiting outside,
you showered and cleaned?
LEE!
Okay.
Give me some coffee.
How nice!
It's all dried up.
You don't paint any more?
No.
What's this?
I drew it long ago.
You're an artist.
Stop it.
You're better
than our art teacher.
You could've been a great artist.
Why don't you come up here?
It's okay.
It's getting late.
Aren't you going home?
Why?
I have to return it tonight.
Come up here
and sit next to me.
I'll turn it back on then.
This is nice.
Move your head.
I don't want to.
Wait!
I'm going to be late.
Don't wait.
Once a year?
They have sex only once a year.
And today must be it.
Hello?
Don't hang up.
You're killing me.
It's not true, is it?
They say I seduced
and stalked you.
They say you said that.
You didn't, did you?
CHOI?
No fun, is it?
Yeah, I'm having fun.
I don't think so.
You teach, right?
No, that's...
Yeah
She teaches
geography at Gyungll.
Oh...
Isn't that school
in a poor area?
Right, but she's moving soon
to Jell High.
That's a good school.
What college did you go to?
One in Seoul.
Her father runs a big farm
down in the south.
Wow...
I truly loved you.
What do you call this then?
You have no idea
what you're putting me through.
You told me you loved me.
We were drunk and got caught up
in the moment.
How could you do this to me?
What does your heart say?
I have to go.
I'll pay you back what I owe you.
You slept with me.
What am I supposed to do?
Damn, keep it up
and I'll have you expelled.
They won't believe you.
You told them I was a stalker.
You told them
to watch out for me.
I give the school a bad name.
I understand
why you're doing this.
But it's breaking my heart.
It hurts me so much.
You're so late.
I was freezing to death.
You have no umbrella.
Why didn't you go?
I missed you.
Let go.
You're getting wet.
Cut it out.
I'm in a bad mood.
So leave.
Let's drink.
I bought some.
That girl who jumped
off the building...
That's you, isn't it?
So you...
You were left with a broken heart.
Are you crying?
Are you?
Let me look at you.
You went through my stuff?
I didn't mean to.
Bastard!
You're not over him yet?
Says who?
Why cry then?
Because I'm so upset
with myself.
It means you still have
feelings for him.
You still love him, don't you?
Asshole!
You recorded it to cherish it,
or what?
I recorded it...
...to leave evidence
that he stole from me.
But you didn't mention
anything about money.
"What does your heart say?"
You were crying for love.
Why are you telling me this?
Just because.
You're pathetic.
I can't believe
you're not over a jerk like him.
Get out!
Go away!
What?
Get the hell out.
What'd I do wrong?
Get out, asshole!
Look at yourself.
You're still in love with a man
who didn't even love you.
Crying out of missing him...
You think I miss him?
If not, why cry?
Say you broke up
with your girlfriend.
She made up stories
to turn you into a stalker.
And you got fired.
How would you feel?
Because of him,
I'm working under you
as a student teacher.
I can't even sleep at night
because the pain is so unbearable.
You think I'm not over him?
I would cut off his limb
if I could.
His wife and the kids...
I want to kill them all!
He didn't like you.
He just fucked you.
You're no different.
What?
Nothing but leeches
sucking blood out of girls.
What the fuck did you say?
You just wanted to fuck me.
So did he.
You two are no different!
Fuck!
Asshole.
Why the fuck are you
taking it out on me?
Say that to him.
Tell him he's a fucking leech
to his face!
Get out of here.
Beat it.
Your lies disgust me.
Get the hell out!
Yeah, I'm fucking leaving.
You really don't know
why I'm doing this?
Get out of my face.
Where are you?
The art teacher at your school
went to KwangJin Univ, right?
Yes.
Find out about
the assistant professor.
Why?
Somebody asked me.
Who?
It's just...
I hear he's an asshole.
He takes money from his students
and all that.
So what?
I just want to see
what that asshole looks like.
I can't sleep.
I need you.
Hui-jung, I have to go.
See you later.
- Yu-lim!
- I'll Tell you later.
Bye!
I can't find your place.
Where are you?
You were here yesterday.
It's dark and pissing rain.
Meet me outside your place.
What?
You sure you have insomnia?
You sleep like a log!
I don't know.
You make me sleepy.
What perfume is this?
I don't wear it.
But I can feel it.
You always smell good.
It makes me drowsy.
I've never slept well
since I moved to Seoul.
With the lights off,
I have bad dreams.
With the lights on, it feels like
someone's watching me.
So I stay up through the night.
Anyway...
It's so nice
that I can sleep tight.
What are you saying?
You don't like me.
I help you sleep well.
So you're using me, right?
Exactly.
That's what you're good for.
Hand.
Forget it.
Why can't we get off
in front of the school?
It's a 20-minuite-walk
from here.
What if people see us?
We'll tell them
we just shared the cab.
I'll walk then.
He's not here yet?
No.
If the principle finds out,
he's in big trouble.
Let's go.
Good morning!
What time do you think it is?
You're always late.
- Oh, You're early.
- Yes.
I hear your eye rolling.
No cheating, okay?
They hang out here.
This is like their hideout.
I often come here
and smoke their cigarettes.
It reminds me of the old days.
We can pack a lunch and eat here.
Why don't you?
How about sweet and sour chicken?
No chicken.
I can't even touch it.
Just thinking about it...
Didn't you hear it?
I heard something.
What?
I bet I heard it.
Hey, cigarettes are gone!
Who could it be?
I bet it's those guys again.
Again?
We should teach them a lesson.
Let's kick their asses!
Hand!
6 missed calls-KIM Yeon-ho
It's turned off.
Leave a message and press #.
There's someone else.
Be well.
I'm sorry.
Press 1 for an instance message
or 2 for recording.
Or 3 for a new message.
It's been cancelled.
We need to talk.
Call me.
Okay, fine.
Let me pee first.
There's a rumor at school.
What rumor?
So funny.
That you and CHOI are
going out.
- Really?
- Yes.
We were being careful.
How'd they find out?
The kids these days are
so quick.
What?
Let me tell you.
I like her.
Asshole!
How can you do that?
What?
You have Hui-jung.
She's like family to me.
CHO.
It's hard for me too.
You...
You can't do this to her.
You can't.
Son of a bitch!
I don't know what to do!
CHO.
It hurt a lot.
I thought you broke my jaw.
Did you drink a lot?
You son of a...
CHO,
This isn't easy for me either.
What am I...
Shut up
and check out
the school website.
What for?
Just do it, asshole.
Stop lying, man.
You're such a bluff.
Guys, it's HONG.
Hi!
What are you doing here?
Let me tell you.
You have beautiful legs.
They look like frog legs
from a distance.
LEE and CHOI leaving a motel
HONG got into LEE's pants.
CHOI's Dirty Past
She stalked a married man
and got expelled.
CHOI slept with
all the male teachers.
CHOI is a home wrecker.
Get down.
Get down!
Move.
- I'll tell you everything!
- No, you don't have to.
Go get her.
CHOI Hong
Yeah?
Where are you?
Let me call you back.
Listen, punks.
If I don't catch who did it,
you're all expelled.
I'll kill not only you,
but also your parents.
- Got that?
- Yes.
Louder!
Like I told you,
If you lie, you'll get expelled.
- Got that?
- Yes.
The student teacher of your class
said that?
Why'd she tell you that?
That's not it.
What is it then?
I overheard it
in the faculties' bathroom.
What were you doing there?
Ours was too crowded.
Tell me what you heard.
That she's doing you.
Says who?
The literature teacher.
What else did she say?
Say it!
That CHOI got kicked out of school
for sleeping with a married man.
So you spread the made-up stories?
Are you nuts?
Come here.
Bitches like you don't
have to study.
Go home.
You'll be expelled.
Don't come back to school!
Can we talk for a second?
CHOI and I had so much
in common that we...
You guys sleep together?
No way!
Never.
So that married guy thing is true.
CHOI was framed.
Says who?
CHOI did?
She told you that herself?
Look, KIM.
I don't know why I have to
tell you about my private life.
I understand you're upset
because you're Hui-jung's friend.
Hui-jung and I...
we have been
together for 6 years now.
All these years,
it's been more than being good.
It still is.
But this means there's no trust.
It's my fault.
I must've done something
to make her doubt me.
But there's nothing
between CHOI and me.
You know the grapevine is
very well established here.
You should've been careful.
You should've dealt with her
in a more professional way.
It seems like
CHOI has a crush on you.
No, she has a fiancé.
I'm sure CHOI is having
a rough time over this.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
I was just so upset.
Hui-jung was crying and...
I'm really sorry
about this whole thing.
Hi.
Coming back from lunch?
Excuse me.
Anything happened
between you and LEE?
You're unbelievable.
The school is upside-down...
due to you.
What?
I understand you liked him
as a man...
... because he was so nice to you
and all that.
I don't blame you.
But you have a fiancé.
Did LEE tell you that?
Did he say
that I liked him?
He denied it, of course.
He was very worried
and protective about you.
I heard about the incident
at your old school.
What did LEE say about me?
That the rumor wasn't true.
And that he was only helping you
as your counselor.
Yu-lim.
Answer my question honestly.
Okay.
Did you tell KIM?
What?
About CHOI.
CHOI?
That student teacher?
Yes.
No, I did not.
You didn't?
What about her?
I just talked to KIM.
Stop fucking lying to me!
Spill the beans!
You asked me to check out
that assistant professor.
It wasn't his fault.
Everybody says so.
What?
She's a slut.
She made advances on him.
She's a home wrecker,
a total psycho.
She hit on you too, didn't she?
Are you okay?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
Do you like her?
Get out of here, asshole!
Go!
It's CHOI!
She's a nutcase.
She turns me off!
What a slut!
I can't believe she's a stalker.
She's disgusting.
You should've controlled
your temper.
We persuaded their parents
not to press charges.
All you need to do is write
a letter of apology.
Okay.
You're kind of old
for a student teacher.
That story on the net...
Is it true?
Are you seeing each other?
No, that's not it.
It's just that we had good feelings
for each other.
Also, we're in charge of
same class.
After all, I'm her counselor.
So we've become friends.
And the kids kind of blew it
out of proportion.
So you are not together?
Well, it sounds like nothing.
Let's wrap this up.
You're off the hook now.
- Bad luck happen sometimes.
- Come on, let's go.
- It's alright.
- Don't worry about it.
You'll be fine.
I have something to tell you.
The truth is...
LEE molested me.
Unlike he said,
I have no feelings for him.
He used his position
as a counselor to molest me.
He forced me to drink
with him.
When I refused it,
he groped me at work.
He harassed and threatened me.
He even came to my place.
CHOI, what are you talking about?
You broke the window
and stole keys from me
and let yourself into my place.
Didn't you?
No, that's not it.
I have a fiancé.
And I heard that...
He said he had a fiancé
and harassed me.
You call that being nice?
You used your position
to molest a woman.
Let's go have a talk.
Let's talk outside.
- Okay, hold on.
- Let's go.
CHOI!
We need to talk.
- Come on, let's go.
- Give me a second.
- CHOI!
- You'll be fine.
CHOI, we need to talk!
CHOI was molested.
LEE raped her!
- Really?
- Yeah, It's true.
The police are here!
She's coming!
What a pity!
Hello?
CHOI, it's over.
He's been fired.
What?
He completely fooled us.
I can't believe that jerk.
I don't know how he even
became a teacher.
You don't have to be ashamed.
Just think of it as bad luck.
We're all worried about you.
You know we're on your side.
Let's break up.
Don't do this now.
I stayed up all night operating.
There's someone else.
You slept with him?
Yes.
Listen.
This is very important.
It's on the SAT every year.
Learn it by heart
by the end of the class.
Okay?
It's cold.
I'm leaving.
Look.
You smoked in class again?
What are you talking about?
I received a complaint again.
Okay.
The competition is really fierce.
You can't keep doing this.
Hello?
- I'm out of here.
- Wait.
It's for you.
Who is it?
Hello?
It went dead.
Who was it?
It was a girl.
A girl?
Yeah.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I work for a friend of mine.
He opened a private institute.
What are you doing here?
I'm going somewhere.
I see.
You got a perm?
Yeah...
Bitch!
You're a bitch.
A bitch like you...
I can kill you right now.
But I'm not dirtying my hands.
All I did was like you.
And this is what I get?
What'd I do wrong?
What did I do for you
to mess my life up?
I liked you too.
Fuck you!
You can't fool me.
You call yourself a human?
How could you do that
to someone that you liked?
Wanna sleep with me?
Crazy bitch!
Are you nuts?
I wanna sleep with you.
Let me tell you.
You can't fool me again.
After what happened,
I'm too frightened to date.
It's all your fault!
So I'll take the responsibility.
Don't even think
about toying with me.
After tonight,
I don't wanna see you again.
If you see me on the street,
don't even say hi.
If you do, I'll kill you.
Crazy bitch!
You're gonna get it!
I sleep well now.
Even without you...
After a few years of insomnia.
Good for you.
You don't need me now.
Let go of my arm.
You sleep well, right?
Let go.
So I thank you.
You're laughing?
You're up.
What happened?
You passed out last night.
It was so hard to drag you here.
Damn, I remember nothing.
I don't know.
Move your arm.
It's stifling.
It snowed!
The first snow of the year!
We're the first to step on it.
It's so pretty!
Gosh!
Are you okay?
My legs are shaky.
- How embarrassing.
- Why'd you fall?
It's slippery.
I don't feel very good.
I should stop drinking.
Why'd you drink so much?
You don't know?
Because of what you've done to me!
I feel burn in my stomach.