1
00:00:30,280 --> 00:00:31,113
than way

2
00:01:15,116 --> 00:01:17,493
Open your ears

3
00:01:18,036 --> 00:01:19,244
to hear the people

4
00:01:21,664 --> 00:01:23,540
Calm thy heart

5
00:01:24,834 --> 00:01:27,127
first for the affairs of the nation

6
00:01:28,379 --> 00:01:38,472
"THE CONCUBINE"

7
00:01:46,940 --> 00:01:48,148
This's really

8
00:01:48,483 --> 00:01:50,275
say nothing

9
00:01:50,652 --> 00:01:51,693
Fool

10
00:01:51,986 --> 00:01:53,779
He is such a reckless lad

11
00:01:55,824 --> 00:01:58,408
Perhaps your son should join us

12
00:01:58,576 --> 00:02:01,411
NO, sir! He is not my son, sir

13
00:02:01,663 --> 00:02:03,539
He once saved my life

14
00:02:03,790 --> 00:02:05,374
at war

15
00:02:05,792 --> 00:02:08,210
so I took him in like a son

16
00:02:11,047 --> 00:02:13,048
How scary!

17
00:02:13,466 --> 00:02:15,092
-The prince is but a thief!

18
00:02:15,635 --> 00:02:16,802
-How dare you!

19
00:02:17,053 --> 00:02:18,011
Fool!

20
00:02:18,221 --> 00:02:19,054
you

21
00:02:20,140 --> 00:02:21,557
Let him go at once!

22
00:02:23,476 --> 00:02:25,811
What have I done wrong?

23
00:02:26,271 --> 00:02:29,148
There is an order to catching deer, too?

24
00:02:30,150 --> 00:02:31,191
How dare you!

25
00:02:31,734 --> 00:02:34,153
-Lock him away at once! -Yes, sir!

26
00:02:34,529 --> 00:02:35,404
Kwon-yoo?

27
00:02:50,295 --> 00:02:51,170
I apologize

28
00:02:51,546 --> 00:02:53,630
for the disturbance,

29
00:02:53,923 --> 00:02:55,883
Your Highness

30
00:02:56,801 --> 00:02:58,218
Please forgive me

31
00:03:06,728 --> 00:03:08,687
Wait until the guest has left

32
00:03:12,609 --> 00:03:13,567
Why?

33
00:03:16,321 --> 00:03:17,487
What worries you so?

34
00:03:21,659 --> 00:03:22,826
Don't worry

35
00:03:30,460 --> 00:03:33,462
I do not hear you reading these days

36
00:03:35,840 --> 00:03:38,926
Just rumors of you wandering...

37
00:03:39,177 --> 00:03:40,302
...out in mad hunting

38
00:03:41,304 --> 00:03:42,888
To not fall weak, men not only

39
00:03:43,223 --> 00:03:46,391
study but hunt and...

40
00:03:51,272 --> 00:03:52,981
That is not what I meant

41
00:03:54,734 --> 00:03:57,110
Why do you frequent Deputy-Minister...

42
00:03:57,528 --> 00:03:58,987
...Shin's house?

43
00:04:00,156 --> 00:04:01,365
Because of his daughter?

44
00:04:07,538 --> 00:04:09,790
A mere deputy-minister's girl?

45
00:04:15,964 --> 00:04:17,339
I've never felt this way before

46
00:04:17,590 --> 00:04:19,883
The court is always critical
of the king's half brother

47
00:04:20,093 --> 00:04:22,052
Stay away from her

48
00:04:23,930 --> 00:04:25,973
It is only right that

49
00:04:27,058 --> 00:04:29,893
I visit you often,

50
00:04:30,728 --> 00:04:32,562
stepmother

51
00:04:32,897 --> 00:04:34,773
You still call me stepmother, sire?

52
00:04:36,401 --> 00:04:38,402
I fret you come

53
00:04:38,778 --> 00:04:40,362
to keep watch on me

54
00:04:42,448 --> 00:04:43,782
Of course not

55
00:04:44,158 --> 00:04:45,784
With no son and

56
00:04:46,035 --> 00:04:47,536
not even a concubine

57
00:04:48,913 --> 00:04:52,165
They say I'm stopping you

58
00:04:53,251 --> 00:04:56,253
with ulterior motives

59
00:04:57,422 --> 00:05:00,299
It is only because

60
00:05:00,591 --> 00:05:03,302
I feel sorry to my late queen

61
00:05:03,511 --> 00:05:06,763
Though I am a stepmother,

62
00:05:11,227 --> 00:05:12,477
I have my courtly duties

63
00:05:13,354 --> 00:05:18,066
I shall see to it immediately

64
00:05:20,028 --> 00:05:23,530
Then, please find a new queen for me

65
00:05:51,893 --> 00:05:53,477
Since you went against the court,

66
00:05:53,895 --> 00:05:55,854
you must run for life

67
00:05:57,148 --> 00:05:58,565
I'm not going

68
00:05:59,859 --> 00:06:01,109
anywhere alone

69
00:06:02,737 --> 00:06:04,446
But there's nothing

70
00:06:04,739 --> 00:06:05,947
I can do for you

71
00:06:15,458 --> 00:06:17,209
Just stay with me

72
00:07:22,233 --> 00:07:22,858
Kwon-yoo!

73
00:07:24,318 --> 00:07:25,026
Kwon-yoo!

74
00:07:26,154 --> 00:07:26,903
Kwon-yoo!

75
00:07:28,322 --> 00:07:29,156
Kwon-yoo!

76
00:07:29,449 --> 00:07:30,615
Escort her away!

77
00:07:31,033 --> 00:07:32,868
Kwon-yoo!

78
00:07:35,705 --> 00:07:36,413
No!

79
00:07:36,622 --> 00:07:37,080
No!

80
00:07:37,957 --> 00:07:38,915
Let go!

81
00:07:39,959 --> 00:07:41,209
Kwon-yoo!

82
00:07:42,587 --> 00:07:43,503
-Hwa-yeon!

83
00:07:44,589 --> 00:07:45,839
-Kwon-yoo! -Hwa-yeon!

84
00:07:46,799 --> 00:07:47,841
No!

85
00:07:48,134 --> 00:07:49,092
Kwon-yoo!

86
00:07:59,479 --> 00:08:00,687
No, Father!

87
00:08:01,022 --> 00:08:02,481
I suggested we run away

88
00:08:02,773 --> 00:08:04,191
Kwon-yoo is innocent!

89
00:08:04,609 --> 00:08:06,568
If this gets known,

90
00:08:06,861 --> 00:08:08,236
not only he

91
00:08:08,613 --> 00:08:10,864
we'll all die

92
00:08:11,115 --> 00:08:12,365
Please let him go

93
00:08:13,201 --> 00:08:14,784
It's too late

94
00:08:15,328 --> 00:08:16,369
-Guards!

95
00:08:17,872 --> 00:08:19,581
I'll go in the palace!

96
00:08:20,833 --> 00:08:24,586
If Kwon-yoo dies, so will I!

97
00:08:29,842 --> 00:08:30,759
-Hwa-yeon!

98
00:08:34,263 --> 00:08:35,597
What have you done to her!

99
00:08:36,224 --> 00:08:38,225
Hwa-yeon!

100
00:09:16,013 --> 00:09:17,138
I will do it

101
00:09:19,308 --> 00:09:22,102
There are rules and steps to bathing, too

102
00:09:24,021 --> 00:09:26,606
I have no right to my own body?

103
00:09:32,113 --> 00:09:36,116
Your Majesty Prince Sung-won is here

104
00:09:37,285 --> 00:09:39,119
It's been so long

105
00:09:40,663 --> 00:09:42,956
How've you been, brother?

106
00:09:44,917 --> 00:09:47,502
Just roaming here and there, sire

107
00:09:53,926 --> 00:09:56,720
please take care

108
00:09:57,722 --> 00:09:59,264
I'm ashamed to see you

109
00:09:59,682 --> 00:10:01,683
so weak and pale, sire

110
00:10:03,477 --> 00:10:06,813
I feel much better seeing you

111
00:10:11,027 --> 00:10:12,819
How are things outside?

112
00:10:14,822 --> 00:10:17,490
The grain and crops have

113
00:10:18,701 --> 00:10:20,744
fully ripened, sire

114
00:10:21,662 --> 00:10:23,413
Your people are making spirits

115
00:10:24,248 --> 00:10:26,207
with chrysanthemums

116
00:10:45,019 --> 00:10:48,146
Recently, he's been ill quite often

117
00:10:49,440 --> 00:10:51,566
I'm afraid the court physician

118
00:10:52,109 --> 00:10:53,818
does not know why

119
00:10:56,238 --> 00:10:57,906
He'll regain his health soon

120
00:10:58,449 --> 00:11:00,450
Don't fret, Your Majesty

121
00:11:02,536 --> 00:11:03,995
You left so suddenly

122
00:11:05,164 --> 00:11:06,539
I was worried

123
00:11:09,585 --> 00:11:11,628
You worried about me?

124
00:11:17,677 --> 00:11:20,303
How foolish of me to worry you both

125
00:11:20,721 --> 00:11:23,098
I'm glad you've returned safely

126
00:11:24,308 --> 00:11:25,767
I came upon hearing

127
00:11:26,185 --> 00:11:27,811
His Majesty's ill

128
00:11:28,604 --> 00:11:31,064
I shall leave when he recovers

129
00:11:34,652 --> 00:11:36,403
It'd be a burden on you and

130
00:11:37,321 --> 00:11:39,572
my nephew for me to stay

131
00:11:40,408 --> 00:11:41,700
What burden?

132
00:11:42,159 --> 00:11:44,119
His Majesty welcomes you so

133
00:11:58,843 --> 00:12:00,301
I've taken up too much of your time,

134
00:12:00,803 --> 00:12:02,762
Your Majesty

135
00:12:19,613 --> 00:12:21,948
Let's listen to the court physician

136
00:12:23,576 --> 00:12:25,702
He's grown weak from boils

137
00:12:26,078 --> 00:12:28,121
and can't eat well

138
00:12:28,414 --> 00:12:30,749
Perhaps it's the food!

139
00:12:31,000 --> 00:12:32,625
If so,

140
00:12:32,918 --> 00:12:34,461
we must interrogate

141
00:12:34,712 --> 00:12:36,588
the royal kitchen matron!

142
00:12:37,339 --> 00:12:39,340
That's preposterous

143
00:12:39,550 --> 00:12:41,468
We can always do that after

144
00:12:41,927 --> 00:12:46,097
His Majesty recovers

145
00:12:46,515 --> 00:12:48,057
We must get to the truth

146
00:12:48,350 --> 00:12:50,143
behind His Majesty's illness

147
00:12:54,690 --> 00:12:55,690
Your Majesty!

148
00:12:56,484 --> 00:12:59,027
His Majesty's state is critical

149
00:12:59,403 --> 00:13:01,654
Please come another day

150
00:13:01,864 --> 00:13:03,072
What do you mean?

151
00:13:03,407 --> 00:13:04,741
I am His Majesty's mother!

152
00:13:05,451 --> 00:13:06,367
Step aside

153
00:13:06,577 --> 00:13:07,410
Your Majesty!

154
00:13:08,579 --> 00:13:10,079
Why do you keep me...

155
00:13:10,414 --> 00:13:11,873
...from meeting my ailing son!

156
00:13:13,584 --> 00:13:16,711
I must see how he is at once!

157
00:13:17,505 --> 00:13:20,673
His Majesty must rest now

158
00:13:20,966 --> 00:13:23,092
Ask her to go for today

159
00:13:24,053 --> 00:13:25,470
Is the queen implying that

160
00:13:26,013 --> 00:13:27,806
I'd interfere in his health?

161
00:13:30,935 --> 00:13:33,186
-My acupuncture set! Hurry!

162
00:13:33,771 --> 00:13:34,729
-Yes, sir

163
00:13:49,995 --> 00:13:51,746
He isn't breathing!

164
00:13:52,790 --> 00:13:55,083
Don't just watch! Do something!

165
00:14:14,854 --> 00:14:16,980
This is a vital spot

166
00:14:35,291 --> 00:14:38,418
-Please appoint your successor!

167
00:14:38,794 --> 00:14:40,962
-Please, Your Majesty!

168
00:15:10,910 --> 00:15:14,329
Your Majesty!

169
00:15:15,497 --> 00:15:17,540
Your Majesty!

170
00:15:19,543 --> 00:15:22,587
Your Majesty!

171
00:15:22,922 --> 00:15:25,590
Your Majesty!

172
00:15:28,677 --> 00:15:31,471
Your Majesty!

173
00:15:32,264 --> 00:15:40,563
Your Majesty!

174
00:15:41,023 --> 00:15:42,857
Your Majesty!

175
00:15:52,284 --> 00:15:55,328
Farewell, My King!

176
00:15:57,039 --> 00:16:00,667
Farewell, My King!

177
00:16:02,044 --> 00:16:05,380
Farewell, My King!

178
00:16:05,589 --> 00:16:08,007
Well done, Minister Yoon

179
00:16:09,343 --> 00:16:12,845
But the prince and queen are still alive

180
00:16:13,639 --> 00:16:15,640
The queen's father also

181
00:16:16,058 --> 00:16:18,518
has many followers

182
00:16:29,071 --> 00:16:32,323
How hard can a woman and her child be?

183
00:16:35,703 --> 00:16:38,496
Without the Left-State Minister
and her father,

184
00:16:39,123 --> 00:16:41,416
she won't last

185
00:16:47,464 --> 00:16:48,631
Majesty!

186
00:16:49,133 --> 00:16:50,925
We must push ahead

187
00:16:51,176 --> 00:16:52,802
before the Queen Mother

188
00:16:53,846 --> 00:16:56,097
She has the power to appoint the next king

189
00:16:56,974 --> 00:16:59,726
They are not to be messed with

190
00:17:01,186 --> 00:17:02,395
Majesty!

191
00:17:02,813 --> 00:17:04,188
If you're ousted here,

192
00:17:04,440 --> 00:17:05,440
you and the prince

193
00:17:05,691 --> 00:17:08,693
will be in danger

194
00:17:10,070 --> 00:17:10,987
By the way

195
00:17:12,448 --> 00:17:14,115
This is the royal kitchen's log

196
00:17:14,825 --> 00:17:16,993
There's nothing around

197
00:17:17,369 --> 00:17:19,078
the day of the king's sudden illness

198
00:17:20,205 --> 00:17:22,081
That means...

199
00:17:22,332 --> 00:17:25,043
Yes. The matron who records

200
00:17:25,836 --> 00:17:28,254
the log is also missing

201
00:17:28,922 --> 00:17:31,382
She must be hidden away
somewhere inside the palace

202
00:17:32,009 --> 00:17:32,967
Inside here?

203
00:17:33,218 --> 00:17:34,385
Yes

204
00:17:34,636 --> 00:17:37,555
We must find her and prove

205
00:17:37,806 --> 00:17:40,475
His Majesty was assassinated

206
00:17:41,393 --> 00:17:43,978
With proof,
I can gather up forces with some ministers

207
00:17:44,313 --> 00:17:46,022
How dare you!

208
00:17:46,315 --> 00:17:49,192
They're conspirators of

209
00:17:49,526 --> 00:17:50,651
high...

210
00:17:50,944 --> 00:17:52,945
...treason!

211
00:17:53,572 --> 00:17:54,655
-Seize them!

212
00:17:54,823 --> 00:17:55,490
-Yes, sir!

213
00:17:55,741 --> 00:17:57,033
High treason?

214
00:17:58,160 --> 00:18:00,286
Why you!

215
00:18:00,788 --> 00:18:02,747
Have you no fear of heaven!

216
00:18:03,874 --> 00:18:06,000
There is a new heaven now!

217
00:18:06,543 --> 00:18:08,753
The queen's father is charged with treason!

218
00:18:09,338 --> 00:18:10,338
What?

219
00:18:10,756 --> 00:18:12,965
The Queen Mother has ordered

220
00:18:13,175 --> 00:18:14,550
his arrest for treason

221
00:18:15,552 --> 00:18:16,636
Fools!

222
00:18:18,138 --> 00:18:20,098
How dare you!

223
00:18:20,432 --> 00:18:21,307
Go away at once!

224
00:18:21,683 --> 00:18:22,600
Over there!

225
00:18:32,986 --> 00:18:33,986
Fools!

226
00:18:43,455 --> 00:18:45,164
This color was made

227
00:18:45,457 --> 00:18:48,126
with red sage in lye

228
00:18:48,585 --> 00:18:50,753
It must be soaked hundreds of times

229
00:18:51,421 --> 00:18:55,466
to get this bright,

230
00:18:56,343 --> 00:18:58,427
blood-like color

231
00:18:58,720 --> 00:19:00,972
It absorbs all other colors
to shine even brighter

232
00:19:01,974 --> 00:19:03,432
It's the king's color

233
00:19:07,479 --> 00:19:09,814
Your Majesty!

234
00:19:29,334 --> 00:19:32,211
It hasn't been long since

235
00:19:32,504 --> 00:19:34,172
His Majesty's been crowned

236
00:19:34,548 --> 00:19:36,507
Thus, the court eunuchs
will also stand guard for a while

237
00:19:54,985 --> 00:19:56,360
Your Majesty

238
00:19:57,279 --> 00:20:00,656
Lie to the left of the queen

239
00:20:05,537 --> 00:20:06,662
Your Majesty

240
00:20:07,456 --> 00:20:11,959
Lie over her with your heart to the left

241
00:20:13,629 --> 00:20:17,381
Lick and suckle her lips

242
00:20:17,716 --> 00:20:18,841
then swallow her saliva, sire

243
00:20:19,301 --> 00:20:22,261
Then, caress down farther

244
00:20:24,848 --> 00:20:28,226
Softly rub her lower stomach

245
00:20:28,602 --> 00:20:30,228
Wait

246
00:20:30,729 --> 00:20:33,314
until her breasts harden,

247
00:20:34,942 --> 00:20:37,693
then grasp

248
00:20:38,195 --> 00:20:39,862
them firmly,

249
00:20:40,197 --> 00:20:42,949

sire

250
00:20:44,534 --> 00:20:45,534
Your Majesty

251
00:20:46,536 --> 00:20:49,247
Begin intercourse, sire

252
00:20:50,666 --> 00:20:52,291
The queen must grab his waist

253
00:20:52,584 --> 00:20:55,461
and accept

254
00:20:55,837 --> 00:20:57,964
his royal penis

255
00:20:59,132 --> 00:21:00,132
I am ready,

256
00:21:00,634 --> 00:21:02,301

sire

257
00:21:02,970 --> 00:21:04,804
Let it in

258
00:21:21,113 --> 00:21:23,281
Go slowly, sire

259
00:21:40,799 --> 00:21:43,592
Next is the anal position

260
00:22:12,622 --> 00:22:13,289
Not yet, sire!

261
00:22:13,582 --> 00:22:14,623
Not yet, sire!

262
00:22:15,125 --> 00:22:16,334
You must ejaculate later

263
00:22:16,626 --> 00:22:17,668
You must ejaculate later

264
00:22:18,045 --> 00:22:19,712
to impregnate a son

265
00:23:57,727 --> 00:23:58,561

sire

266
00:24:02,524 --> 00:24:05,067
Please return to your chambers,

267
00:24:07,946 --> 00:24:08,863

sire

268
00:24:09,364 --> 00:24:11,073
If the Queen Mother knew...

269
00:24:17,080 --> 00:24:18,122
What happened?

270
00:24:18,874 --> 00:24:21,709
I couldn't say a word in the royal kitchen

271
00:24:22,502 --> 00:24:25,504
The maids run away when they see me

272
00:24:31,136 --> 00:24:33,345
We must find the royal kitchen matron

273
00:24:39,978 --> 00:24:40,811
Your Highness?

274
00:24:41,688 --> 00:24:42,771
You found something?

275
00:24:43,773 --> 00:24:44,690
Tell me

276
00:24:45,567 --> 00:24:46,734
Well,

277
00:24:47,861 --> 00:24:49,653
if she is still alive...

278
00:24:53,408 --> 00:24:56,869
I once heard the eunuchs whispering

279
00:24:58,246 --> 00:25:00,247
Past the Queen Mother's court

280
00:25:01,458 --> 00:25:03,334
and the laundry place

281
00:25:03,919 --> 00:25:06,670
I heard there is a secret

282
00:25:08,131 --> 00:25:09,632
pathway underground

283
00:25:10,300 --> 00:25:11,884
No sunlight can get through,

284
00:25:12,135 --> 00:25:14,178
But it snows all day there

285
00:25:16,348 --> 00:25:17,723
And only

286
00:25:18,225 --> 00:25:20,893
the Queen Mother's private soldiers

287
00:25:21,686 --> 00:25:23,187
know of it

288
00:25:47,504 --> 00:25:48,337
Your Highness!

289
00:25:50,090 --> 00:25:50,714
Your Highness!

290
00:25:51,841 --> 00:25:52,675
Your Highness!

291
00:25:52,968 --> 00:25:55,427
Please get me out of here

292
00:25:56,304 --> 00:25:58,973
I just did as I was told

293
00:25:59,224 --> 00:26:00,057
Calm down

294
00:26:02,519 --> 00:26:03,310
Calm down

295
00:26:04,145 --> 00:26:04,895
And take a look at this

296
00:26:10,068 --> 00:26:11,527
Did you write this?

297
00:26:12,571 --> 00:26:13,696
Yes, Your Highness

298
00:26:16,533 --> 00:26:17,074
But

299
00:26:17,284 --> 00:26:20,953
Do you remember what

300
00:26:22,914 --> 00:26:23,789
His Majesty ate that day?

301
00:26:24,207 --> 00:26:27,293
He had lunch at the Queen Mother's court

302
00:26:28,545 --> 00:26:29,837
The Queen Mother?

303
00:26:34,134 --> 00:26:36,468
She suddenly called His Majesty

304
00:26:36,761 --> 00:26:39,346
and ordered us not to prepare lunch

305
00:26:42,142 --> 00:26:42,850
Why?

306
00:26:43,935 --> 00:26:45,436
Is it not to your liking?

307
00:26:45,729 --> 00:26:46,979
It's because

308
00:26:48,565 --> 00:26:50,357
I have indigestion

309
00:26:50,609 --> 00:26:54,320
Afraid it's poisoned, sire?

310
00:26:56,239 --> 00:26:56,989
Of course not

311
00:26:57,198 --> 00:26:59,992
They say you are ill

312
00:27:00,243 --> 00:27:02,828
because I'm poisoning you

313
00:27:06,041 --> 00:27:06,832
Then, he had diarrhea

314
00:27:08,460 --> 00:27:09,752
all night

315
00:27:24,059 --> 00:27:28,228
You two dare defile the palace order?

316
00:27:29,606 --> 00:27:32,900
Make sure they never forget

317
00:27:40,909 --> 00:27:42,493
their sins!

318
00:27:42,911 --> 00:27:44,620
Cut off the atrocious fool's penis!

319
00:27:46,081 --> 00:27:49,208
Remove her womb and...

320
00:27:49,459 --> 00:27:50,250
...sew her genitals!

321
00:27:50,543 --> 00:27:52,252
Show them the strict order of the court!

322
00:27:52,629 --> 00:27:53,545
Yes, ma'am!

323
00:28:32,127 --> 00:28:34,962
What brings you to this humble sire?

324
00:28:36,965 --> 00:28:41,218
I haven't visited since you moved to this place

325
00:28:44,139 --> 00:28:45,472
Where did you go at night

326
00:28:45,807 --> 00:28:47,933
with no guards?

327
00:28:48,309 --> 00:28:50,561
My father is locked up

328
00:28:51,479 --> 00:28:53,605
How could I just sit and wait?

329
00:28:54,816 --> 00:28:56,108
I apologize

330
00:28:56,943 --> 00:28:59,695
I've been too busy with things

331
00:29:01,823 --> 00:29:04,241
You must be devastated

332
00:29:04,993 --> 00:29:08,579
I shall see to your father's release

333
00:29:09,956 --> 00:29:10,914
no, thank you

334
00:29:11,499 --> 00:29:13,417
I cannot be a burden on you, sire

335
00:29:14,586 --> 00:29:15,586
I am just grateful

336
00:29:16,129 --> 00:29:20,215
to be alive

337
00:29:26,139 --> 00:29:30,809
It must be uncomfortable in this old place

338
00:29:32,103 --> 00:29:33,520
Chief Eunuch!

339
00:29:38,610 --> 00:29:42,321
Furnish this place suited to Her Highness

340
00:29:42,614 --> 00:29:44,698
That is under jurisdiction

341
00:29:44,991 --> 00:29:47,701
of the Queen Mother, sire

342
00:29:48,328 --> 00:29:48,827
What?

343
00:29:50,163 --> 00:29:51,413
It's her jurisdiction?

344
00:29:55,126 --> 00:29:58,629
So, you won't follow the king's order?

345
00:30:07,096 --> 00:30:08,931
Your Highness! Look this!

346
00:30:13,102 --> 00:30:15,521
His Majesty sent such nice things

347
00:30:18,566 --> 00:30:21,151
Embankment work on Nakdong

348
00:30:21,694 --> 00:30:24,655
River damaged tributary

349
00:30:24,864 --> 00:30:27,991
The peasant shares in great harm

350
00:30:28,576 --> 00:30:32,371
With the rainy season...

351
00:30:32,705 --> 00:30:34,039
...320 homes were lost

352
00:30:34,332 --> 00:30:38,001
And over 200 people went missing

353
00:30:38,211 --> 00:30:41,213
Apart from what's required, reduce the taxes

354
00:30:41,548 --> 00:30:44,341
Order all district magistrates

355
00:30:44,551 --> 00:30:49,221
to send soldiers to help the people

356
00:30:49,556 --> 00:30:52,891
Next is a list of pardoned sinners

357
00:30:53,101 --> 00:30:55,519
in honor of the coronation

358
00:30:57,647 --> 00:30:59,439
Excluding murders and high treason

359
00:30:59,774 --> 00:31:01,066
280 sinners...

360
00:31:01,317 --> 00:31:03,652
...in the capital

361
00:31:04,028 --> 00:31:05,404
and 1 37 elsewhere were...

362
00:31:05,572 --> 00:31:07,406
Do you people not see me?

363
00:31:08,032 --> 00:31:10,534
Why don't you submit reports to me?

364
00:31:10,827 --> 00:31:14,413
While His Majesty learns affairs,

365
00:31:14,831 --> 00:31:15,789
the Queen Mother is...

366
00:31:15,999 --> 00:31:17,416
Does it look like
I'm learning by just sitting here?

367
00:31:18,209 --> 00:31:20,210
From now on, prepare reports

368
00:31:22,005 --> 00:31:24,381
for him to see...

369
00:31:24,799 --> 00:31:25,924
...as well

370
00:31:27,135 --> 00:31:28,093
Continue

371
00:31:28,970 --> 00:31:30,637
Is the queen's father on the list?

372
00:31:47,739 --> 00:31:49,281
Have you lost your mind?

373
00:31:50,241 --> 00:31:51,408
Do you not know for whom

374
00:31:51,784 --> 00:31:54,703
they are being purged?

375
00:31:56,039 --> 00:31:58,957
The former queen's father has many followers

376
00:31:59,626 --> 00:32:02,711
I fret it'll perturb the people

377
00:32:02,962 --> 00:32:06,256
Did she beg you to release
her father when you met?

378
00:32:08,551 --> 00:32:09,968
You kept watch on me?

379
00:32:12,138 --> 00:32:15,557
Though you act as regent, I am still the king

380
00:32:15,767 --> 00:32:16,934
You're not ready

381
00:32:18,227 --> 00:32:20,729
Mentioning personal feelings

382
00:32:21,022 --> 00:32:22,522
at court is no king!

383
00:32:25,735 --> 00:32:27,819
Forgotten how we made it here?

384
00:32:30,615 --> 00:32:33,867
If we don't nip the bud,
we could get hurt again

385
00:32:37,497 --> 00:32:40,499
We almost died when your court was on fire

386
00:32:41,876 --> 00:32:44,086
I've never once forgotten that

387
00:32:44,587 --> 00:32:48,382
Please stop mentioning that

388
00:32:50,760 --> 00:32:53,136
Every woman in the palace is yours, but one!

389
00:32:53,388 --> 00:32:58,892
You can never touch that woman

390
00:33:02,939 --> 00:33:05,524
Bring all the eunuchs
at the former queen's court!

391
00:33:05,775 --> 00:33:07,484
What have I done wrong?

392
00:33:08,069 --> 00:33:10,570
I did all you wanted, Mother

393
00:33:11,030 --> 00:33:12,990
I accepted her as sister-in-law

394
00:33:13,241 --> 00:33:15,200
And became the king as you wished!

395
00:33:15,952 --> 00:33:18,036
What more do you want from me?

396
00:33:41,144 --> 00:33:43,645
If the bee will not shoo away

397
00:33:43,980 --> 00:33:47,232
the flower will be cut off

398
00:33:55,742 --> 00:33:56,950
Get me a drink

399
00:34:32,320 --> 00:34:33,195
Hwa-yeon!

400
00:34:37,075 --> 00:34:39,367
I took you in like my own son

401
00:34:39,869 --> 00:34:41,995
How dare you covet my daughter!

402
00:34:42,205 --> 00:34:44,247
Hwa-yeon!

403
00:34:45,208 --> 00:34:47,918
Remember why I let you live

404
00:34:48,211 --> 00:34:50,462
And never come to us again

405
00:34:50,671 --> 00:34:51,505
-Guards!

406
00:34:52,215 --> 00:34:54,674
-Castrate him at once!

407
00:34:54,884 --> 00:34:55,550
-Yes, sir!

408
00:35:23,287 --> 00:35:24,162
Kwon-yoo?

409
00:35:25,790 --> 00:35:27,499
How did you come here?

410
00:35:35,883 --> 00:35:37,551
I thought you were dead

411
00:35:39,971 --> 00:35:40,595
No.

412
00:35:40,888 --> 00:35:45,142
I prayed every moment for you to be alive

413
00:35:46,018 --> 00:35:47,018
Kwon-yoo

414
00:35:48,896 --> 00:35:50,397
I'm so glad to see you

415
00:35:52,316 --> 00:35:53,942
alive and well

416
00:35:55,945 --> 00:35:57,362
Kwon-yoo died back then,

417
00:35:58,030 --> 00:36:00,073
madam

418
00:36:01,200 --> 00:36:03,076
What do you mean?

419
00:36:03,870 --> 00:36:05,370
Please help me

420
00:36:06,164 --> 00:36:09,374
I have no clue what is happening

421
00:36:11,085 --> 00:36:13,712
I found evidence the king's been murdered

422
00:36:15,298 --> 00:36:17,007
Please, go back

423
00:36:18,926 --> 00:36:23,430
Do you not know I'm Minister Yoon's man?

424
00:36:25,850 --> 00:36:28,185
What do you mean?

425
00:36:34,609 --> 00:36:35,817
You're the only one

426
00:36:37,111 --> 00:36:38,904
I have in the palace

427
00:36:40,364 --> 00:36:41,281
Kwon-yoo

428
00:36:43,242 --> 00:36:44,868
How could you?

429
00:36:48,706 --> 00:36:50,332
How could I be

430
00:36:51,417 --> 00:36:53,501
of any help now?

431
00:36:55,880 --> 00:36:57,923
What more do you want

432
00:36:58,841 --> 00:37:00,592
in life?

433
00:37:04,388 --> 00:37:06,014
If you want to live,

434
00:37:07,808 --> 00:37:09,851
run away alone

435
00:37:12,605 --> 00:37:14,272
Alone again

436
00:37:17,109 --> 00:37:18,443
Like before

437
00:37:21,239 --> 00:37:23,240
Run by yourself

438
00:37:27,912 --> 00:37:29,829
No visitors are allowed

439
00:37:30,248 --> 00:37:34,709
Still, Her Highness is here

440
00:37:35,127 --> 00:37:36,795
Just for a moment?

441
00:37:37,088 --> 00:37:39,714
I could lose my head I'm sorry

442
00:37:43,886 --> 00:37:45,887
Could you at least give this

443
00:37:46,472 --> 00:37:48,139
to my elderly father?

444
00:37:49,600 --> 00:37:50,767
It's rice gruel

445
00:38:18,212 --> 00:38:20,046
Your daughter sent this

446
00:38:36,856 --> 00:38:38,398
You?

447
00:38:41,819 --> 00:38:43,945
How did you come here?

448
00:38:46,532 --> 00:38:50,702
Such a dangerous act

449
00:38:53,956 --> 00:38:58,251
I heard what happened
from the royal kitchen matron

450
00:38:58,586 --> 00:39:01,838
Who should I tell this to?

451
00:39:02,173 --> 00:39:03,131
Look.

452
00:39:03,549 --> 00:39:07,218
I'll die for my sin But not her!

453
00:39:12,016 --> 00:39:13,141
You should've killed me back then

454
00:39:13,726 --> 00:39:16,770
Stop!

455
00:39:23,486 --> 00:39:28,281
Come back!

456
00:39:35,122 --> 00:39:36,790
How is the former queen?

457
00:39:38,376 --> 00:39:41,252
She is well, Your Majesty

458
00:39:43,547 --> 00:39:45,382
Visit her day and night

459
00:39:46,133 --> 00:39:48,385
to make sure she's well

460
00:39:50,596 --> 00:39:51,513
Yes, sire

461
00:39:52,681 --> 00:39:53,973
How dare you?

462
00:39:54,350 --> 00:39:58,228
Persimmon is harmful to His Majesty's boils

463
00:39:59,480 --> 00:40:01,022
What is your name?

464
00:40:01,816 --> 00:40:02,982
Choong-young, sire

465
00:40:03,234 --> 00:40:05,151
How'd you know I have boils?

466
00:40:06,028 --> 00:40:08,363
I knew from how you hesitated

467
00:40:08,697 --> 00:40:10,198
leaning against your back

468
00:40:10,449 --> 00:40:11,199
Tell me,

469
00:40:11,992 --> 00:40:14,285
how can boils be subdued?

470
00:40:14,537 --> 00:40:17,414
Sweat and chills can cause

471
00:40:17,665 --> 00:40:21,084
boils to form easily, sire

472
00:40:21,377 --> 00:40:23,169
It is best to avoid

473
00:40:23,504 --> 00:40:24,921
raw or cold foods

474
00:40:25,131 --> 00:40:26,256
You seem familiar

475
00:40:27,383 --> 00:40:28,842
Have we met before?

476
00:40:29,844 --> 00:40:31,094
No, sire.

477
00:40:31,387 --> 00:40:34,097
How can a lowly man meet His Majesty?

478
00:40:35,516 --> 00:40:37,308
I like this lad

479
00:40:37,768 --> 00:40:40,478
Promote him as senior eunuch

480
00:40:41,772 --> 00:40:45,108
Your Majesty To become a senior,

481
00:40:45,484 --> 00:40:47,485
one must work over 1 6 years

482
00:40:48,404 --> 00:40:51,781
It took him over 20 years
to reach that post to be here

483
00:40:52,199 --> 00:40:54,659
-This man came in recently

484
00:40:54,869 --> 00:40:55,827
-What?

485
00:40:56,370 --> 00:40:59,497
Can't I do as I wish even with a eunuch?

486
00:41:00,207 --> 00:41:02,459
Why?

487
00:41:02,835 --> 00:41:04,586
Do you only follow the Queen Mother, too?

488
00:41:05,588 --> 00:41:07,005
As you wish, sire

489
00:41:23,814 --> 00:41:26,232
What brings Your Highness here this late?

490
00:41:28,444 --> 00:41:29,652
Is it this?

491
00:41:30,237 --> 00:41:31,237
Kwon-yoo

492
00:41:32,031 --> 00:41:34,616
They will be beheaded at dawn

493
00:41:35,826 --> 00:41:37,911
Why make the effort?

494
00:41:39,788 --> 00:41:43,458
The poor kitchen matron died because of you

495
00:41:49,507 --> 00:41:51,549
Madam? What is it?

496
00:41:52,468 --> 00:41:56,304
I must watch my father die

497
00:41:56,639 --> 00:41:59,265
for we couldn't die with the king

498
00:41:59,642 --> 00:42:02,810
Please kill us first, sire

499
00:42:03,604 --> 00:42:05,522
Beheading the former queen's father

500
00:42:05,898 --> 00:42:07,899
is too harsh

501
00:42:08,817 --> 00:42:10,276
Please take back the order

502
00:42:11,946 --> 00:42:13,530
The court has already decided

503
00:42:16,784 --> 00:42:18,618
Please save her father!

504
00:42:19,370 --> 00:42:21,454
I will do whatever you want

505
00:42:23,040 --> 00:42:25,250
I will no longer seek her!

506
00:42:25,459 --> 00:42:29,587
Loyal ministers wish this
to stabilize your reign!

507
00:42:31,423 --> 00:42:32,882
No further discussion

508
00:42:38,639 --> 00:42:40,014
Who do you speak of?

509
00:42:42,476 --> 00:42:45,603
The relatives on your side who all hold posts?

510
00:42:53,237 --> 00:42:55,572
She must suffer so because

511
00:42:55,906 --> 00:42:57,991
the late king didn't kill us?

512
00:42:58,242 --> 00:42:59,576
Watch what you say!

513
00:42:59,827 --> 00:43:04,706
Am I this nation's king at all?

514
00:43:07,209 --> 00:43:08,626
Not this time

515
00:43:09,837 --> 00:43:12,046
It won't be as you wish

516
00:43:13,257 --> 00:43:13,965
Sire!

517
00:43:14,300 --> 00:43:15,508
-Chief Eunuch?

518
00:43:15,884 --> 00:43:17,010
-Yes, sire

519
00:43:18,304 --> 00:43:21,097
Run and stop the execution

520
00:43:22,975 --> 00:43:23,850
Sire!

521
00:43:24,685 --> 00:43:27,061
Changing the Queen Mother's order will...

522
00:43:34,361 --> 00:43:35,236
Then, you go!

523
00:43:38,824 --> 00:43:40,158
No judgments

524
00:43:40,784 --> 00:43:42,285
That is not up to us

525
00:43:58,218 --> 00:44:01,262
All hear His Majesty's command!

526
00:44:01,722 --> 00:44:04,057
Shin Ik-chul and his men

527
00:44:04,391 --> 00:44:06,684
have plotted high treason

528
00:44:07,186 --> 00:44:09,520
And endangered the court

529
00:44:10,314 --> 00:44:11,814
By law,

530
00:44:12,191 --> 00:44:15,443
their entire family

531
00:44:15,694 --> 00:44:17,779
must die and...

532
00:44:18,530 --> 00:44:20,782
Wretched fool!

533
00:44:21,158 --> 00:44:24,452
You poisoned the late king to death!

534
00:44:25,329 --> 00:44:26,371
Off with his head!

535
00:44:54,316 --> 00:44:55,066
Step aside!

536
00:44:56,193 --> 00:44:58,069
I must speak with her!

537
00:44:58,362 --> 00:44:59,153
Your Majesty

538
00:45:00,406 --> 00:45:01,155
Sire!

539
00:45:02,074 --> 00:45:03,116
Please calm down

540
00:45:03,534 --> 00:45:04,409
Why you!

541
00:45:47,745 --> 00:45:50,329
Perhaps it's best to go, sire

542
00:46:01,967 --> 00:46:04,469
It is obvious for whom they plotted treason

543
00:46:04,928 --> 00:46:06,512
Depose the former queen

544
00:46:06,764 --> 00:46:09,599
and banish her and her son

545
00:46:10,225 --> 00:46:11,976
Your Majesty

546
00:46:12,352 --> 00:46:18,024
Please punish the former queen
to avoid any future harm

547
00:46:19,610 --> 00:46:21,444
Our king isn't coming again?

548
00:46:24,490 --> 00:46:25,907
Your Majesty

549
00:46:26,450 --> 00:46:28,826
Please give the order

550
00:46:32,122 --> 00:46:34,290
Please give the order!

551
00:46:34,500 --> 00:46:36,626
Find reason against her
to persuade the king first!

552
00:46:39,630 --> 00:46:40,755
Dismissed

553
00:46:43,467 --> 00:46:44,634
Your Majesty

554
00:46:45,052 --> 00:46:50,056
Please depose and banish them

555
00:46:51,266 --> 00:46:52,558
His Majesty has arrived

556
00:46:56,605 --> 00:46:57,605
Stay here

557
00:46:58,941 --> 00:47:00,441
Please return

558
00:47:00,734 --> 00:47:02,026
during the day, sire

559
00:47:03,445 --> 00:47:04,904
I heard you are ill

560
00:47:05,823 --> 00:47:07,990
With my father's head up on the street,
how can I be well?

561
00:47:08,325 --> 00:47:09,534
how can I be well?

562
00:47:12,037 --> 00:47:13,579
Is that why you avoid me so?

563
00:47:18,669 --> 00:47:19,836
Do you know

564
00:47:20,587 --> 00:47:22,588
what is happening in the court?

565
00:47:22,840 --> 00:47:24,757
I know very well,

566
00:47:25,342 --> 00:47:27,635
Sire!

567
00:47:27,886 --> 00:47:29,512
Those dying to banish me

568
00:47:29,847 --> 00:47:31,305
will be avid to find you here

569
00:47:31,473 --> 00:47:32,348
So please

570
00:47:33,725 --> 00:47:37,353
Do not come for me again

571
00:47:38,522 --> 00:47:40,314
How can you be so cruel?

572
00:47:41,567 --> 00:47:43,818
Why do you think I endure being on the throne?

573
00:47:44,361 --> 00:47:46,362
For what?

574
00:47:47,489 --> 00:47:49,365
Why put me in such misery?

575
00:47:51,910 --> 00:47:53,536
Yell at me instead

576
00:47:53,787 --> 00:47:56,163
For stealing my nephew's seat

577
00:47:56,456 --> 00:47:59,250
and letting your father die!

578
00:47:59,793 --> 00:48:02,587
Say you are angry!

579
00:48:12,556 --> 00:48:13,723
What is your name?

580
00:48:14,600 --> 00:48:17,059
It's Geum-ok, Your Majesty

581
00:48:18,061 --> 00:48:21,397
Why? Will you take her to your chambers?

582
00:48:25,068 --> 00:48:26,569
Why not, madam

583
00:48:31,658 --> 00:48:33,409
Does she resent me greatly?

584
00:48:36,413 --> 00:48:38,164
She is torn by the loss

585
00:48:39,875 --> 00:48:41,500
She cannot eat

586
00:48:43,003 --> 00:48:45,087
She is devastated

587
00:48:48,759 --> 00:48:50,009
Go on

588
00:48:51,553 --> 00:48:54,597
How does she look before sleeping?

589
00:48:54,890 --> 00:48:55,765
Pardon?

590
00:48:57,559 --> 00:48:59,977
Well,

591
00:49:00,354 --> 00:49:04,482
she changes her clothes

592
00:49:08,528 --> 00:49:10,321
She unties her hair

593
00:49:12,532 --> 00:49:16,869
And sleeps in a white dress

594
00:49:18,664 --> 00:49:20,706
Who undresses her?

595
00:49:22,250 --> 00:49:23,751
I do, sire

596
00:49:25,253 --> 00:49:26,796
How do you undress her?

597
00:49:28,090 --> 00:49:29,840
Well,

598
00:49:30,842 --> 00:49:34,345
I untie the breast-tie

599
00:49:35,180 --> 00:49:36,806
-Do you bathe her, too?

600
00:49:37,015 --> 00:49:38,849
-Yes, sire

601
00:49:39,184 --> 00:49:40,518
How do you bathe her?

602
00:49:41,520 --> 00:49:43,813
She goes into

603
00:49:45,857 --> 00:49:47,316
a scented hot tub

604
00:49:47,609 --> 00:49:49,193
Where do you wash her first?

605
00:49:51,321 --> 00:49:55,491
With a fine cloth

606
00:49:55,826 --> 00:49:56,951
I wash her breasts and shoulders

607
00:49:57,244 --> 00:49:58,244
Is she soft?

608
00:49:59,746 --> 00:50:03,833
Yes, she is so soft and white

609
00:50:04,042 --> 00:50:05,167
Go on

610
00:50:05,502 --> 00:50:07,253
When she gets up,

611
00:50:07,838 --> 00:50:09,213
I wash between her legs

612
00:51:05,604 --> 00:51:06,687
Your Majesty

613
00:52:28,353 --> 00:52:30,229
This is your new room, madam

614
00:52:31,648 --> 00:52:34,024
You've gained His Majesty's favor,

615
00:52:34,317 --> 00:52:36,402
but have yet to be a concubine

616
00:52:36,778 --> 00:52:38,487
Please mind your conduct

617
00:52:38,738 --> 00:52:41,240
and do not wander from this room

618
00:52:42,159 --> 00:52:43,325
Yes, ma'am

619
00:52:47,581 --> 00:52:48,664
I see

620
00:52:52,252 --> 00:52:56,422
She will be your maid

621
00:53:12,022 --> 00:53:14,064
bringing harm upon yourself

622
00:53:14,441 --> 00:53:16,609
How I upset you not knowing

623
00:53:17,235 --> 00:53:19,236
the great pains I've caused

624
00:53:21,156 --> 00:53:22,156
No, madam

625
00:53:23,992 --> 00:53:24,909
I, too, have been upset over

626
00:53:25,869 --> 00:53:29,246
what happened to your father

627
00:53:29,998 --> 00:53:34,210
What harm does the Queen Mother

628
00:53:34,544 --> 00:53:37,588
think my son and I could be?

629
00:53:38,715 --> 00:53:39,757
Madam

630
00:53:50,936 --> 00:53:54,104
Forgive me about your father

631
00:53:59,486 --> 00:54:01,820
How could I blame you, sire?

632
00:54:03,573 --> 00:54:06,283
I must not be fit to be king

633
00:54:08,703 --> 00:54:10,704
What do you mean, sire?

634
00:54:12,791 --> 00:54:14,625
The late king always said

635
00:54:14,918 --> 00:54:18,379
you had the wisdom and morals

636
00:54:21,132 --> 00:54:23,217
Why the Queen Mother's regency?

637
00:54:24,719 --> 00:54:29,265
What a shame and a pity

638
00:54:31,685 --> 00:54:35,646
It's time you gave orders to depose them,
Your Majesty

639
00:54:38,358 --> 00:54:40,567
He visited the former queen?

640
00:54:47,909 --> 00:54:51,704
Do you know anything about poison?

641
00:54:53,331 --> 00:54:57,293
I once saw poisonous aconite
while with ginseng diggers

642
00:55:17,856 --> 00:55:20,733
Having this inside the palace -Means trouble

643
00:55:21,526 --> 00:55:26,071
But to those who don't know, it's just a rock

644
00:55:30,785 --> 00:55:33,370
Know how to make poison with that?

645
00:55:34,622 --> 00:55:35,622
-By burning it, sir

646
00:55:36,082 --> 00:55:37,541
-Then, make it

647
00:55:39,002 --> 00:55:41,628
If the mother and son won't leave,

648
00:55:42,422 --> 00:55:46,133
there's only one way out of here

649
00:56:09,616 --> 00:56:11,742
You deal with where His Majesty sleeps?

650
00:56:12,410 --> 00:56:13,494
Me?

651
00:56:15,330 --> 00:56:17,247
I wouldn't dare

652
00:56:17,457 --> 00:56:19,541
Could you lead him to me

653
00:56:19,876 --> 00:56:21,585
on the 3rd?

654
00:56:22,879 --> 00:56:23,796
-Please, madam

655
00:56:24,005 --> 00:56:24,963
-Who knows?

656
00:56:25,215 --> 00:56:28,467
If I give birth to a prince,
you'll be the chief eunuch

657
00:56:39,479 --> 00:56:41,522
People are so cunning

658
00:56:42,148 --> 00:56:46,026
When you go up, you don't want to get down

659
00:56:47,112 --> 00:56:48,654
Right, Your Highness?

660
00:56:48,947 --> 00:56:50,489
With His Majesty's favor,

661
00:56:50,782 --> 00:56:52,699
who says I can't become a queen?

662
00:56:53,034 --> 00:56:54,368
How dare you!

663
00:56:55,245 --> 00:56:56,870
Watch your words, madam

664
00:56:57,789 --> 00:56:59,873
You dare tell me what to do?

665
00:57:05,672 --> 00:57:08,841
With the king's favor who would I help?

666
00:57:09,968 --> 00:57:12,094
Would I do anything to harm you?

667
00:57:16,099 --> 00:57:17,641
Of course

668
00:57:18,476 --> 00:57:21,103
How can I help?

669
00:57:21,396 --> 00:57:23,981
I should adorn myself to catch his eye

670
00:57:25,358 --> 00:57:26,525
I need jewelry

671
00:57:27,527 --> 00:57:30,863
Take whatever you think you'll need

672
00:57:56,514 --> 00:57:57,681
What are you doing!

673
00:57:59,267 --> 00:58:03,562
I am not only your son, but the king

674
00:58:05,440 --> 00:58:09,151
What king?
When you don't come to the assemblies!

675
00:58:09,444 --> 00:58:10,777
You don't give me a chance to do anything

676
00:58:11,196 --> 00:58:12,488
You make all the decisions

677
00:58:12,947 --> 00:58:15,699
Now, you want me to be a puppet?

678
00:58:15,992 --> 00:58:18,452
When things settle and you have an heir,

679
00:58:20,330 --> 00:58:22,623
I will...

680
00:58:22,874 --> 00:58:24,416
...step down

681
00:58:24,709 --> 00:58:26,084
When will that be?

682
00:58:28,338 --> 00:58:29,213
What?

683
00:58:29,881 --> 00:58:32,633
Why don't you just sit on the throne, Mother?

684
00:58:34,219 --> 00:58:37,554
I am sick of sleeping
with the queen before you!

685
00:58:38,181 --> 00:58:41,892
I just have to sow the seeds?

686
00:58:42,936 --> 00:58:45,187
It doesn't have to be the queen

687
00:58:47,023 --> 00:58:48,440
An auspicious day?

688
00:58:50,151 --> 00:58:51,693
I'll give the concubines a chance!

689
00:58:52,654 --> 00:58:53,403
Who is it?

690
00:58:54,072 --> 00:58:57,157
It's Lady Geum-ok, sire

691
00:59:10,129 --> 00:59:11,004
bitch

692
00:59:14,717 --> 00:59:15,551
Let's go

693
00:59:18,596 --> 00:59:20,055
Why you!

694
00:59:21,599 --> 00:59:24,434
Your Majesty

695
00:59:24,811 --> 00:59:27,187
Why do you have this?

696
00:59:27,438 --> 00:59:30,023
Your Majesty, please...

697
00:59:30,316 --> 00:59:31,858
Sire! I can explain...

698
00:59:32,860 --> 00:59:33,610
Your Majesty!

699
00:59:36,114 --> 00:59:37,990
I have something to say, sire

700
00:59:44,455 --> 00:59:47,332
Tell me why you have this!

701
00:59:56,134 --> 00:59:58,260
There's something you must know.
Why was this in someone else's hand?

702
01:00:00,388 --> 01:00:03,098
Please calm your anger and have a seat, sire

703
01:00:03,349 --> 01:00:05,434
Don't you know how I feel?

704
01:00:07,604 --> 01:00:09,479
Do you detest me that much?

705
01:00:11,941 --> 01:00:12,983
Am I...

706
01:00:14,402 --> 01:00:17,321
no better than that eunuch?

707
01:00:20,325 --> 01:00:21,158
Drag him in

708
01:00:25,663 --> 01:00:27,497
He seemed familiar

709
01:00:28,374 --> 01:00:29,666
He was the fool who lived in your house!

710
01:00:30,001 --> 01:00:31,627
You disguised him...

711
01:00:32,086 --> 01:00:33,754
...as a eunuch?

712
01:00:34,380 --> 01:00:35,756
-That's preposterous

713
01:00:36,007 --> 01:00:39,176
-Explain yourself!

714
01:00:40,178 --> 01:00:42,220
Why is that fool here!

715
01:00:42,513 --> 01:00:44,890
I didn't know he was here

716
01:00:45,224 --> 01:00:46,391
until recently, Your Majesty

717
01:00:46,601 --> 01:00:48,810
You expect me to believe that?

718
01:00:51,606 --> 01:00:55,275
I remember how he used to look at you!

719
01:00:56,152 --> 01:00:58,111
You and that fool!

720
01:01:04,077 --> 01:01:07,204
Who's the father of your prematurely born son?

721
01:01:08,289 --> 01:01:10,582
Is he my brother's son or not?

722
01:01:12,460 --> 01:01:13,960
Undress him

723
01:01:14,420 --> 01:01:16,880
I must see if he is a eunuch or not!

724
01:01:17,090 --> 01:01:19,925
Must you humiliate me like this?

725
01:01:20,802 --> 01:01:21,593
Strip him!

726
01:01:23,137 --> 01:01:25,639
Sire. Why would you see something so hideous?

727
01:01:56,838 --> 01:01:59,506
Please leave, sire

728
01:02:08,474 --> 01:02:11,518
Don't you know how I feel?

729
01:02:12,729 --> 01:02:15,188
Do you really think I don't know?

730
01:02:19,652 --> 01:02:23,655
When the Queen Mother watches so viciously...

731
01:02:25,658 --> 01:02:28,994
Queen Mother or not, I don't know care!

732
01:02:30,830 --> 01:02:33,915
Look at me. I'm a wreck

733
01:02:34,250 --> 01:02:36,251
I want you so!

734
01:02:52,935 --> 01:02:54,144
Sire

735
01:03:01,194 --> 01:03:02,194
Sire

736
01:03:04,781 --> 01:03:05,864
Sire

737
01:03:14,040 --> 01:03:16,416
When you become a true king,

738
01:03:17,210 --> 01:03:18,919
please return then

739
01:03:27,470 --> 01:03:29,179
I shall become a king

740
01:03:29,806 --> 01:03:32,474
I shall become a true king

741
01:03:40,399 --> 01:03:43,485
He broke family morals and...

742
01:03:47,240 --> 01:03:49,115
No one must know of this

743
01:03:50,451 --> 01:03:51,451
Yes, Your Majesty

744
01:03:52,245 --> 01:03:54,746
You know very well, sir

745
01:03:56,999 --> 01:04:01,711
What I had to do to seat him on the throne

746
01:04:03,464 --> 01:04:04,923
Get rid of her

747
01:04:25,486 --> 01:04:28,697
You shot 40 times

748
01:04:29,407 --> 01:04:30,574
Think of...

749
01:04:36,289 --> 01:04:38,206
You called, Your Majesty?

750
01:04:46,340 --> 01:04:49,467
Let's see how good you are

751
01:04:50,261 --> 01:04:52,512
I dare not hold

752
01:04:52,972 --> 01:04:54,222
Give him a bow

753
01:05:05,484 --> 01:05:06,067
Kwon-yoo

754
01:05:10,448 --> 01:05:13,116
Why'd you come into the palace?

755
01:05:14,160 --> 01:05:16,453
Becoming a court eunuch
was the only way I had,

756
01:05:16,704 --> 01:05:17,954

sire

757
01:05:20,666 --> 01:05:23,460
A eunuch dare loved the queen?

758
01:05:24,420 --> 01:05:26,713
Of course not, sire

759
01:05:29,342 --> 01:05:31,176
I must see the former queen

760
01:05:32,345 --> 01:05:34,429
I acted disrespectfully last night,

761
01:05:35,264 --> 01:05:36,890
so I must see her

762
01:05:38,225 --> 01:05:42,437
The Queen Mother...

763
01:05:42,772 --> 01:05:43,772
...is sick in bed

764
01:06:49,171 --> 01:06:51,131
I'm not drinking that decoction again

765
01:06:51,340 --> 01:06:52,549
But, Your Majesty

766
01:06:52,967 --> 01:06:58,471
The Queen Mother
makes sure you drink this every day

767
01:06:58,639 --> 01:06:59,973
Then, you drink it

768
01:07:00,808 --> 01:07:02,017
Pardon?

769
01:07:02,685 --> 01:07:05,020
But we don't even eat garlic

770
01:07:05,396 --> 01:07:07,772
to curb our libido, sire

771
01:07:08,107 --> 01:07:10,025
If I drink that decoction, I am afraid...

772
01:07:11,068 --> 01:07:12,110
Oh.

773
01:07:14,280 --> 01:07:16,197
Eunuchs have sexual drive?

774
01:07:17,491 --> 01:07:19,576
We can't have erections

775
01:07:20,077 --> 01:07:24,998
but still feel sexual desires, sire

776
01:07:28,586 --> 01:07:29,169
Choong-young

777
01:07:30,671 --> 01:07:31,629
You drink it

778
01:07:34,759 --> 01:07:36,885
Why? You can't?

779
01:07:37,636 --> 01:07:39,512
Afraid to be sexually aroused?

780
01:07:41,307 --> 01:07:42,390
Drink it

781
01:08:10,294 --> 01:08:12,170
I won't endanger my son

782
01:08:13,756 --> 01:08:15,215
I'll protect him no matter what

783
01:08:15,716 --> 01:08:17,342
No worries

784
01:08:34,235 --> 01:08:37,612
Yours is completely gone

785
01:08:48,624 --> 01:08:50,625
It can't be!

786
01:08:54,046 --> 01:08:55,839
Who is it?

787
01:08:57,550 --> 01:09:00,343
Who ordered this? Please calm down, sire

788
01:09:01,053 --> 01:09:03,638
I do not know anything, sire

789
01:09:04,598 --> 01:09:08,143
I just got the medicine
and decocted it as usual

790
01:09:09,854 --> 01:09:10,979
Your Majesty...

791
01:09:15,860 --> 01:09:18,027
Anyone who speaks of this

792
01:09:18,404 --> 01:09:20,405
shall be beheaded!

793
01:09:21,157 --> 01:09:22,991
Call the physician in secret

794
01:09:25,953 --> 01:09:30,081
Save him I have something to hear from him

795
01:09:36,255 --> 01:09:38,423
Forgive me, sire!

796
01:09:39,049 --> 01:09:42,051
I do not know anything

797
01:09:42,344 --> 01:09:43,136
Show the evidence

798
01:09:44,763 --> 01:09:46,306
Do you recognize it?

799
01:09:46,765 --> 01:09:48,433
It was found in your room

800
01:09:49,768 --> 01:09:52,395
I really don't know, sire

801
01:09:57,109 --> 01:09:59,235
Did the Queen Mother say to kill me?

802
01:09:59,486 --> 01:10:03,323
Then, who is in charge of

803
01:10:04,366 --> 01:10:06,284
the medicinal herbs?

804
01:10:07,703 --> 01:10:10,622
It's Minister Yoon, sire

805
01:10:20,716 --> 01:10:22,258
No one is allowed in, sir

806
01:10:22,593 --> 01:10:23,343
I promise

807
01:10:23,719 --> 01:10:25,386
I'll bring the prince back safely

808
01:10:26,513 --> 01:10:28,640
We'll soon meet again

809
01:10:29,016 --> 01:10:30,558
Don't fret, Your Highness

810
01:10:35,231 --> 01:10:38,107
Mother! I don't want to go!

811
01:10:38,817 --> 01:10:40,193
Mother!

812
01:10:40,736 --> 01:10:42,487
Mother!

813
01:10:43,197 --> 01:10:44,989
Mother!

814
01:10:47,534 --> 01:10:49,619
That is nothing but the truth?

815
01:10:49,870 --> 01:10:52,830
I wouldn't dare lie to you, Your Majesty

816
01:10:54,833 --> 01:10:56,542
She deceived a eunuch's child

817
01:10:56,835 --> 01:10:58,378
for the king's son?

818
01:11:00,339 --> 01:11:03,049
And became a queen?

819
01:11:06,845 --> 01:11:08,263
Wretched whore!

820
01:11:10,557 --> 01:11:11,432
Come in!

821
01:11:15,354 --> 01:11:16,479
Yes, Your Majesty

822
01:11:17,106 --> 01:11:18,439
Send her to the dungeon

823
01:11:27,032 --> 01:11:29,075
Me?

824
01:11:32,371 --> 01:11:39,002
Your Majesty! I'll go back to being a maid!

825
01:11:39,378 --> 01:11:41,337
Please, not the dungeon!

826
01:11:41,672 --> 01:11:44,632
I'd rather die than go there!

827
01:11:46,260 --> 01:11:47,093
Kill her

828
01:11:48,971 --> 01:11:54,892
But, Your Majesty! No!

829
01:11:55,853 --> 01:12:01,441
Let me go!

830
01:12:02,067 --> 01:12:03,318
Why're you doing this to me?

831
01:12:06,613 --> 01:12:10,700
Please save me, Your Majesty!

832
01:12:12,244 --> 01:12:15,204
Let go! No!

833
01:12:16,290 --> 01:12:18,666
I don't want to die!

834
01:12:27,259 --> 01:12:29,552
You sent away the soldiers I sent?

835
01:12:30,471 --> 01:12:33,264
How can you send soldiers to your mother?

836
01:12:34,183 --> 01:12:37,894
I must really be a puppet king

837
01:12:39,730 --> 01:12:40,772
Right

838
01:12:41,690 --> 01:12:43,900
You liked that seat so much,

839
01:12:44,943 --> 01:12:48,112
you cut me up...

840
01:12:49,531 --> 01:12:51,491
...into a puppet

841
01:12:52,201 --> 01:12:53,493
Now, you'll get rid of me?

842
01:12:58,248 --> 01:12:58,873
What do you mean?

843
01:12:59,333 --> 01:13:00,541
Did you give the order to poison me?

844
01:13:02,127 --> 01:13:03,169
What?

845
01:13:04,755 --> 01:13:06,464
The physician confessed

846
01:13:08,342 --> 01:13:11,260
You plotted with Yoon to kill me?

847
01:13:13,055 --> 01:13:13,971
What?

848
01:13:15,099 --> 01:13:17,767
-That's preposterous! -Isn't it?

849
01:13:19,186 --> 01:13:21,229
I thought it was strange

850
01:13:22,856 --> 01:13:24,690
Your man, Yoon, couldn't have

851
01:13:25,067 --> 01:13:27,276
plotted this alone!

852
01:13:29,363 --> 01:13:30,738
This is a trap!

853
01:13:34,159 --> 01:13:35,785
The former queen is up to this

854
01:13:36,662 --> 01:13:37,870
That wretch!

855
01:13:38,080 --> 01:13:44,710
Right. Now, I see

856
01:13:46,672 --> 01:13:49,882
Poison the decoction

857
01:13:50,175 --> 01:13:51,717
than frame her?

858
01:13:54,304 --> 01:13:55,555
Kill me,

859
01:13:56,515 --> 01:13:59,392
her, and my nephew?

860
01:14:02,312 --> 01:14:05,189
Then, who did you plan to seat here?

861
01:14:05,816 --> 01:14:07,108
What do you mean?

862
01:14:09,486 --> 01:14:11,404
Minister Yoon and...

863
01:14:11,780 --> 01:14:14,198
...I lived to put you on that throne!

864
01:14:17,453 --> 01:14:20,830
You lasted quite long

865
01:14:23,250 --> 01:14:24,208
-Kill her! -Yes, sir!

866
01:14:34,595 --> 01:14:35,553
-Who are you!

867
01:14:55,491 --> 01:14:59,410
Seize everyone one of the traitors!

868
01:14:59,661 --> 01:15:00,870
Traitors!

869
01:15:24,478 --> 01:15:26,979
Do you know what she did?

870
01:15:28,232 --> 01:15:30,316
The late king couldn't have children

871
01:15:30,692 --> 01:15:32,944
Be honest for once!

872
01:15:37,074 --> 01:15:38,574
Have you forgotten?

873
01:15:39,576 --> 01:15:42,119
The late queen died while giving birth!

874
01:15:45,249 --> 01:15:46,999
I poisoned him since

875
01:15:48,919 --> 01:15:52,129
-The prince's birth is dubious

876
01:15:55,175 --> 01:15:59,136
-What?

877
01:16:08,981 --> 01:16:11,107
You poisoned my brother?

878
01:16:11,775 --> 01:16:13,067
Who asked you to do that?

879
01:16:15,195 --> 01:16:17,822
For whom!

880
01:16:20,909 --> 01:16:24,829
For whom did you do that!

881
01:16:26,164 --> 01:16:29,000
When did I ever say I wanted to be king!

882
01:16:33,839 --> 01:16:36,716
My child... Look at me

883
01:16:44,391 --> 01:16:46,559
It was all to protect you

884
01:16:46,935 --> 01:16:48,853
in this cruel palace

885
01:16:49,271 --> 01:16:52,231
I'm your mother

886
01:16:57,446 --> 01:17:00,239
Why'd you force me on the throne

887
01:17:02,242 --> 01:17:05,453
and turn me into someone
who can't trust his mother?

888
01:17:06,330 --> 01:17:08,706
You can't trust me?

889
01:17:16,089 --> 01:17:19,508
You dare defy your mother!

890
01:17:25,015 --> 01:17:26,515
If you all meet,

891
01:17:27,142 --> 01:17:28,768
the truth will come out

892
01:17:30,187 --> 01:17:31,646
Guards!

893
01:17:33,231 --> 01:17:37,193
Bring Minister Yoon and Kwon-yoo at once!

894
01:17:37,653 --> 01:17:38,903
That won't happen!

895
01:17:39,112 --> 01:17:40,863
Yes, it will!

896
01:17:46,203 --> 01:17:47,119
Minister Yoon!

897
01:17:58,840 --> 01:18:00,466
I brought the criminals as ordered,
Your Majesty

898
01:18:01,009 --> 01:18:03,636
The physician confessed

899
01:18:07,265 --> 01:18:08,974
Evidence was found in his room

900
01:18:10,769 --> 01:18:12,853
Who do you think he said

901
01:18:13,563 --> 01:18:15,856
was behind this?

902
01:18:16,274 --> 01:18:20,027
How would I know, sire?

903
01:18:20,320 --> 01:18:21,570
Why can't you say it!

904
01:18:22,489 --> 01:18:24,615
I do not know anything

905
01:18:25,659 --> 01:18:29,662
I drank the decoction, did I not?

906
01:18:29,955 --> 01:18:31,664
Then, why'd you hesitate

907
01:18:31,998 --> 01:18:33,916
when I told you to drink it!

908
01:18:34,835 --> 01:18:36,752
You knew it was poisoned, didn't you!

909
01:18:36,962 --> 01:18:38,671
Enough! Stop it!

910
01:18:38,922 --> 01:18:41,841
I'm asking this fool a question!

911
01:18:43,885 --> 01:18:45,594
You knew!

912
01:18:46,680 --> 01:18:48,472
How'd you know it was poisoned?

913
01:18:49,516 --> 01:18:50,182
Sire!

914
01:18:50,851 --> 01:18:52,810
Do you know what she did?

915
01:18:54,646 --> 01:18:57,398
She defiled the royal court

916
01:18:57,858 --> 01:19:00,025
with that fool!

917
01:19:01,111 --> 01:19:03,654
Drag her here to confess!

918
01:19:04,406 --> 01:19:05,448
Yes!

919
01:19:07,367 --> 01:19:08,743
I'm guilty

920
01:19:09,870 --> 01:19:12,580
Guilty for bearing the late king's son

921
01:19:13,623 --> 01:19:15,583
And guilty for being alive

922
01:19:15,834 --> 01:19:20,087
You're guilty for this uproar due to your son

923
01:19:20,964 --> 01:19:23,591
And guilty for distracting the king!

924
01:19:26,720 --> 01:19:27,928
But, Your Majesty

925
01:19:29,014 --> 01:19:30,514
Who is that man?

926
01:19:32,017 --> 01:19:34,185
He's Minister Yoon's man

927
01:19:34,519 --> 01:19:36,479
who killed my father

928
01:19:37,314 --> 01:19:38,981
What daughter would secretly

929
01:19:40,275 --> 01:19:43,110
plot with the enemy?

930
01:19:43,361 --> 01:19:44,278
You wretch!

931
01:19:44,821 --> 01:19:47,782
How dare you show fake tears here!

932
01:19:48,408 --> 01:19:51,118
What would my young child know or do

933
01:19:51,870 --> 01:19:54,663
that I'd covet your throne?

934
01:19:55,332 --> 01:19:57,333
If I thought that in the slightest

935
01:19:58,960 --> 01:20:02,671
I'd bite my tongue and die right here

936
01:20:03,757 --> 01:20:06,008
But I cannot die falsely accused

937
01:20:06,718 --> 01:20:08,844
as someone so shameless

938
01:20:13,975 --> 01:20:15,643
Confess the truth!

939
01:20:15,977 --> 01:20:18,687
Who ordered you to poison the decoction?

940
01:20:34,830 --> 01:20:36,330
The Queen Mother

941
01:20:38,124 --> 01:20:39,375
She ordered me to make

942
01:20:40,168 --> 01:20:42,419
the poison

943
01:20:43,463 --> 01:20:44,463
And Minister Yoon

944
01:20:45,507 --> 01:20:47,174
gave it to...

945
01:20:47,425 --> 01:20:48,175
This is a trap!

946
01:20:48,510 --> 01:20:49,343
It's a trap, sire!

947
01:20:54,683 --> 01:20:55,766
What are you doing?

948
01:20:58,687 --> 01:20:59,728
Why did you do it!

949
01:21:01,231 --> 01:21:02,898
Was the throne that dear

950
01:21:03,567 --> 01:21:05,651
to kill your own son?

951
01:21:06,194 --> 01:21:07,570
Tell me!

952
01:21:08,405 --> 01:21:09,572
Calm down, sire!

953
01:21:10,323 --> 01:21:11,574
She can't breathe!

954
01:21:12,200 --> 01:21:12,908
Sire!

955
01:21:20,625 --> 01:21:24,044
Lock them up

956
01:21:24,588 --> 01:21:25,796
and execute them all!

957
01:21:48,612 --> 01:21:50,905
When you become a true king,

958
01:21:51,781 --> 01:21:53,365
please return then

959
01:22:18,516 --> 01:22:20,017
Is it all done?

960
01:22:21,645 --> 01:22:24,730
Will you accept me now?

961
01:28:38,354 --> 01:28:41,523
Farewell, My King!

962
01:28:43,234 --> 01:28:47,029
Farewell, My King!

963
01:28:48,448 --> 01:28:51,575
Farewell, My King!