This movie is made for ages 18 or older.
Underage viewing prohibited.
English subtitles and timing by elee
I got sick and tire of the horrible subtitle work done by studios.
All subtitle work dedicated to my J
Sit back and enjoy the movie :)
If you enjoyed my subtitle work, drop me a line at
elee@simplymenu.com
Do you need sub work for other movies?
Make your request to elee@simplymenu.com
It's that way.
Open my ears as big as a donkey and
so I may hear what my people are saying.
THE CONCUBINE
Concubine to the King
Korean movie - 2012
Once again, I am so sorry.
That one doesn't know front from back.
It would have been nice to have your son join us, as well.
No, not at all.  He isn't my son at all.
When I was at the war front, he saved my life once
so I brought him back and treat him like my own son.
You've ruined his hunting game. Let's go.  Now.
I'm so afraid. *** sarcastically ***
What?  A prince? He is nothing but a thug!
You are unworthy of being here!
You there!  Take your hands off of him.
What have I done to deserve this?
Are you saying even the deer is first for the prince?
Why you still...!
Take him out and lock him in the storage.
Yes sir.
Is that you, Kwon-yoo?
Please forgive me.  I've wrong you by not teaching the lower ones.
Please forgive me.
I told you to stay away from here 'til he leaves.
What? What are you worried about?
Don't worry.
I hear you are not reading lately.
Is it true that you your time is consumed by hunting?
I was trying to broaden my view like
others by not focusing on study alone...
Was I really asking you that?
What is the reason you keep going to the Shin family's house?
Is it because of his daughter?
Only the Shin family...
She is the first one that I like...
Have you forgotten that the whole palace is
not fond of having a half brother of the king around?
Don't do anything to give them a reason to make it an issue.
It's my rightful duty to see you twice a day.
You still don't call me "mother".
It seem like you are spying on me.
You are making me very uncomfortable.
What do you mean by spying?
You still don't have a heir and have not gotten a concubine
either.  Others are saying I am making you this way.
I'm just sorry for the one who has already passed.
There isn't any other reason.
Although I am your new mother,
you must understand that I still care for you.
Then, please seek out for a new candidate for the queen's position.
I will start seeking a new queen.
Who's out there?
My prince, please, come in.
Oh, my prince.
How...How can you...How can you do this to me?
It's very late.  Let's go inside first.
Didn't you promise me already?
Yes, I have promised you. But I could not go against palace instruction...
Why? Did she say that she doesn't want me?
Please let's step inside first...
Tell her to come out.
Very well.
I will tell her myself. Tell her to come out.
Since you didn't go into the palace, we'll be running for the rest of our lives.
I will never go anywhere by myself alone.
There isn't anything I can do for you.
All I want is to be together.
Kwon-yoo! Kwon-yoo!
Please take her outside.
No, don't. Don't!
Let go. Kwon-yoo!
No, Kwon-yoo! Don't!
No, Father! I told him to flee with me. It wasn't Kwon-yoo's fault.
If this is found out he, as well as all our family, won't survive.
Please, let Kwon-yoo live!
That's already too late.
What are you doing?
Yes sir.
I'll go into the palace.
If Kwon-yoo dies, I will die as well!
Let go of me!
Where are you taking Hwa-yeon? Hwa-yeon! Hwa-yeon!
Let go! Let go!
I'll do it myself.
Even the bathing has proper rules and order.
Do you mean, I don't have freedom over my own body?
*** 5 years later ***
Your Majesty, Seong-won prince is here to see you.
I haven't seen you for a while.  Where have you been, my brother?
I've been wondering without staying in the same place.
Your Majesty, I'm afraid you look so ill.
I haven't been well for a few days,
but seeing you is making me feel much better.
How is the world outside of the palace?
The weather is cold enough to have fruits on the
trees and the colors of autumn are beautiful to see.
Your people are taking chrysanthemum flowers to make wine...
This is happening often, recently.
The royal doctors don't know the reason either.  It's just very frustrating.
He will get better soon.  Your highness need not worry so much.
You left so sudden, I was worried.
You worried about me?
My thoughtlessness made you both worry.
I'm just glad you come back healthy.
I came as soon as I heard of His Majesty's illness.
I'll be leaving as soon as he gets better.
It might be a burden to you and the young prince if I stay in the palace.
What burden? His Majesty is very happy to see you.
I took away too much time as you already have a weary heart.
His body was blue all over...this mean that
there must be someone who's harming him purposely.
What do you mean by harming His Majesty?  Be careful what you say.
Please calm down and let's hear what the doctor has to say.
He's been weak from the tumor and is not eating enough...
Are you sure that there isn't something wrong with his food?
If there is a problem with the food, we need
to investigate the royal chef and find out the truth.
That's right. We should...
You are wrong.  It won't be too late to investigate
after His Majesty gains back some energy.
What are you talking about? We need to find out
the truth in order to prescribe the right treatment to him.
Your Highness, he is extremely ill so please come back at a later time.
What do you mean? I'm his mother.  Move a side.
Your Highness!
What's your intention for preventing me from seeing him?
I need to see his condition with my own eyes.
Please tell the Queen Mother that His Majesty
is not in a condition to see her right now.
Are you saying that I am harming him now?
Go bring the instruments now, hurry.
Yes, sir.
Is he not being able to breath?
Don't just look, please try something.
This is a lethal location.
Your Majesty, please let us know of your successor. Please make your decision.
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty ... Your Majesty ... Your Majesty ...
The king has passed. The king has passed. The king has passed.
You've done well.  You've been most helpful.
But the queen and the young prince survive, as well as the
queen's father who has many follower and is from a warrior clan...
Don't you think I can take care of a woman and a child?
With her father and left minister (war minister) gone, she won't have a chance.
Your Highness, we need to do something before the Queen Mother does something.
The Queen Mother has the right to choose the successor.
Do you think they're that easy to persuade?
Your Highness, if we retreat from here you and the young prince's life could be in danger.
Also, this is the chef's record.  There were no records for the day His Majesty became ill.
You mean ..?
That's right. Even the person who writes the record is missing as well.
There hasn't been enough time for them to take the recorder
out of the palace.  That means, she is hidden somewhere inside of palace.
Inside of palace?
Yes, Your Highness. We need to find the recorder and prove the murder.
The left minister and the others are planning to find the truth.
All we need is to find the proof to assist them.
Who are you fellows? How dare you come...
They all committed a sin of treason.  Arrest all of them.
Yes sir.
Treason?  Yoon-jungho, you bastard!  Aren't you afraid of the heavens?
Now that heaven has changed.
Boo-won Goon (the queen's father's title) come out!  You are under arrest.
What's the matter?
He has committed a sin of treason.  It's an order from the Queen Mother.
How dare you make a loud noise here?  Go away!
Over there.  Catch him.
Take him away.
This red color is made by dipping the cloth in a mixture of flower petals.
It takes hundreds of dippings to make such a vibrant red.
This red is the color that melds all the other
colors, which signifies the color of a King.
Your Majesty.  Your Majesty.
Our duty is not to be part of politics.
We are in charge of His Majesty's wellbeing as well
as maintaining the palace traditions and rules.
We are the hidden hands that allow the palace to function smoothly.
Everything we do is for His Majesty and the palace.
All of you need to remember and remind yourselves of this.
Yes sir.
Since the King is new on the throne, all eunuchs
are to be on standby without any shift changes.
If you stay here His Majesty will be in danger.  Don't move a muscle.
I said, don't move!
Who is that person?
He came with a recommendation from Yoon-jungho Minister.
Yoon-jungho Minister ... hmm.
He is the future of the palace inner power.
What do you mean?
Since you became the Head of Eunuchs, you have become sneaky.
As for you...you may be a rat sitting on top of rice pot
but you never know when your luck will run out.
If you want to stay there for long time, you need
to learn to tame young ones like him.
Worrying about your food bowl, you must be getting old as well.
What would be more important than one's food bowl?
You know, I almost got beheaded this time.
I trust you, so please take care of me in the future as well ... hmm?
Your Majesty, please lay to the left of the queen.
Your Majesty, raise your left side
so that your heart will be higher.
First, kiss the lower lip and suckle it.
Then you must swallow her saliva.
Place your hand on her lower stomach, then start caressing her.
Continue until her breast enlarges...
Then cover her breast with one hand; cover it completely.
Your Majesty, you may start your movement.
The Queen must embrace His Majesty's waist,
then accept his penetration.
Your Majesty, I am ready, so go ahead.
You may feel the pleasure building.
Next, position yourself behind her.
It's not the time yet.
(Queen Mother) It's not time yet.
You can get a son only by finish together.
It's not the time yet.
(Queen Mother) You can get a son only by finish together.
You can get a son only by finish together.
It is time to head to the bed chamber, now.
You Majesty, if the Queen Mother finds out about this ...
What has happened?
I couldn't even ask because of the leery mood in the royal kitchen.
I don't know why but every one's avoiding me.
No matter what, we need to find the head chef.
Your Highness.
Do you know something?
Tell me.
It's just ... if she isn't dead...
I once heard when eunuchs were talking of a place ...
From the basement corridor of the main building, past the
workers area, there is a passage to a lower floor entrance
The place has no daylight and dust snows down all day ...
Oh, and nobody is suppose to know of it or find out but the Queen Mother's army.
You bitch.
As you are a concubine to the past king, why aren't you paying respect to me?
When did I order you to get the food ready?
His Majesty will be coming by soon.
How dare you starve me this way?
Your Highness, why are you out of the eunuch's quarter?
Please put some makeup on and change your cloth as well. Ok?
Very well.
Your Highness!
Your Highness ... Your Highness. Please take me out of here.
All I have done is what was asked of me.
Please, calm down.
Calm yourself and take a look at this.
Is this what you have written?
Yes, Your Highness.
But?
Can you remember what His Majesty ate that day?
On this day, His Majesty ate
lunch at the Queen Mother's quarters.
At the Queen Mother's quarters ...
The Queen Mother called suddenly, he told me not to prepare a meal.
Why, does it not look appetizing?
I just feel a little bit of indigestion.
Why, do you think I would put poison in the food?
Your Highness!
People are saying that I am making you weak by using poison.
And then, His Majesty had diarrhea all night long.
How dare you two break the rules of the palace?
I will remind you of the consequence of undermining the rules.
For him, cut off the rest of his penis.  For her, remove her uterus and
sew her vagina to demonstrate the importance of palace rules.
Look here, your hands are so beautiful.
I know that as well.
Your Majesty.
Who are you?
Please kill me! ***meaning an apology**
I've ask you who you are?
I've committed a sin that's worth dying for. ***meaning an apology**
She is a servant girl who came with the Queen.
Please kill me.  I've committed a sin that's worth dying for.
Your Majesty.  Why have you come to this unworthy place?
Because I've never came by after you move to these quarters.
Such a late night, where did you go without a servant?
My father is imprisoned as a traitor, how can a child sit and idle?
I'm so sorry. I've been so busy with the funeral....
I know you've had hardship.  Don't worry about your father.
I will take care of it.
No. I can't be a burden to Your Majesty.
Just having survived, I am more than grateful.
How uncomfortable are you, using a
building that hasn't been use in long time?
Is there anyone outside?
Call the building master and have him make alterations
to the quarters to match her status.
The Queen Mother ordered the current condition of Her Highness's quarters.
What? The Queen mother's made this decision?
How can the Queen Mother's decisions be taken over my orders?
Your Highness, look at these.
The items sent by His Majesty are wonderful.
This way.
The Nak-Dong River's repair work has polluted the water condition.
Farmers are having a hard time farming in the area.
Also, as a result of the monsoon rain 325 houses were damaged
and more than 200 people are missing or dead.
Take emergency food from 3 states and have the Horse Minister
and Water Minister take military personnel to help those in need.
The next issue is, to celebrate the new Kingship, a
list of people who will be release from the prison ...
280 people from the capital region who
have not committed the murder or treason,
and 137 people from Kung-Gi state.
Do you even see me?
Why don't you have anything for me?
That's because while Your Majesty gains experience,
the Queen Mother will ...
You think just sitting here will make me gain experience?
From now on, take measure to include His Majesty
in the decision making process.
Please, continue.
Is the Boo-won (queen's father) name included in the list?
Are you out of your mind?
For who?
Don't you know for whose benefit I'm getting rid of them?
The Boo-won (queen's father) has a lot of followers.
As there are a lot of misfortunes lately,
I wouldn't want to loose the trust of the people ...
When you went to see the Queen,
did she ask you to have her father release?
Did you spy on me?
Although you have the temporary power
to the throne, I am this nation's King.
You're not there yet.
Having spoken with personal feelings in cabinet meeting ...
do you really think you are ready?
Have you forgotten how we got this far?
If we don't cut the new leaf, we can get hurt later.
Your palace had a fire and we both almost died.
Your mother has never forgotten that incident.
Please ... Please don't repeat that incident again.
Although all of the women in the palace are yours to have,
don't you know there is one woman you can't touch?
Gather all the eunuchs who helped
His Majesty go to the Queen's place.
What did I do wrong?
I did everything Mother has asked me to do.
I took her as sister-in-law, as you asked.
Became a King as you asked.
What else do you want me to do?
If I can't keep the bees from the flower,
I have to remove the flower to solve a problem.
Bring me something to drink.
Let go of me. Let go of me.
I took you in like my own son and kept you
close, how dare you take my daughter?
Hwa-yeon ... Hwa-yeon!
Remember that I let you live.
Don't you ever show your face in front of me.
You there, make sure he can never act as a man again.
Kwon-yoo!  How can you be here?
I thought you were dead.
No, I prayed every moment that you are still alive.
Kwon-yoo, I'm just grateful that you are alive.
Kwon-yoo died then.
Kwon-yoo, what are you talking about?  Please help me.
I don't understand what's going on in the palace.
I've found the proof that the King was murdered.
You must go back.
Don't you know that I am Yoon-jungho Minister's man?
What do you mean by that?
You are my only ally in the palace. Kwon-yoo ...
How can you?
What can I do at this point?
You've gained that position (of Queen).
What more do you want?
If you want to live, you should flee by yourself ...
Just yourself, like last time.
Just like last time.
Flee by yourself.
No one's allowed.
Although that's the situation, Your Highness is here.
Let her see his face, at least.
If something goes wrong, my neck will be gone.
I'm so sorry.
My father is very old,  can you at least give him this?
It's just a porridge.
Your daughter has sent this.
How can you be here?
You have done something very dangerous.
She has done nothing wrong.
I have discovered the truth about that day.
If you tell me who to share the truth ...
Listen!  I'm dying because of my sin, but she ...
It would have been better if you'd killed me back then.
Listen. Listen. Listen!
Is Hwa-yeon Queen's palace alright?
Yes, I heard that she is fine.
Stop by and find out if she needs anything.
Yes sir.
What's going on?
Because of the sore, Your Majesty should not be
eating dried persimmon in fruit punch.
What is your name?
It's Chun-young, Your Majesty.
How did you know that I have a sore?
I knew from the way you hesitated as you
leaned your back, and by the color of your skin.
Then how can one treat a sore?
Hot blood chi circulates faster in heat and stops
when it gets cold, a person with this type of chi gets such sores easily.
Therefore, you must stay away from extreme heat or cold, Your Majesty.
You look familiar, have you seen me before?
I couldn't have.
How can such a lowly one ever have seen Your Majesty before?
Since I like this person, I will promote him to be near me.
Your Majesty!  To be close to you a eunuch must
work for at least 16 years to get the opportunity.
This eunuch alone has worked over 20 years to get that opportunity. How can you
give such an opportunity to a eunuch who just became a main building eunuch.
What?
Don't I have power over a single eunuch?
Why? Are you saying as Head Eunuch,
you will only listen to the Queen Mother?
I will do as you asked, Your Majesty.
Your Highness, what are you doing here at this late hour?
Is this the reason?
Kwon-yoo.
All of them will be killed in the morning anyway.
Why are you trying so hard?
Because of Your Hhighness, the head chef died needlessly early.
Your Highness, what is going on?
Because the young prince and I didn't die with the past king,
we will be witnessing the death of my father.
Kill us both first, instead.
Although he has committed the sin of a traitor, killing him is too harsh a sentence.
Please take back the order.
It's already been decided.
Please let Boo-won live. I will do anything you want.
If you ask me not to see the Queen again, I will not...
It is the will of the other ministers to set an example
for the future. Please don't mention this issue again.
Who do you mean?
You mean those from your family side?
Is my sister-in-law hurting because my own brother didn't get rid of us?
You must speak carefully.
Am I really King of this nation?
This matter will not be done the way you want.
Your Majesty.
Is the Head Eunuch here?
Yes, Your Majesty.
You must hurry and stop the execution.
Your Majesty, you should not go against the Queen Mother's will ...
Then you shall go.
Do not try to decide.  It is not our right.
Prisoner Shin, take this order paper.
Prisoner Shin and all your gang have endanger the kingdom through treason.
In accordance to the law, 3 families from the clan
of each traitorous member will be killed ...
How dare you?
In accordance to the law, 3 families from the clan
of each traitorous member will be killed ...
How dare you?
How dare you talk of the nation as you murder the king?
Carry out the sentence.
Step aside.  I've told you I have something to tell Her Highness.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, Please calm yourself.
Your Majesty should go back now.
Check, this is a hard one to escape.
Let's take a look. It's big problem. Let me take a move back.
You always want a move back.
You think I will give you a move back for nothing.
All I have is a set of balls.  Do you want that?
A set of balls.  That sounds good.  I always wanted them.
You may take 10 moves back if you want.
Did you piss on a frozen foot?  You look like you just stepped in shit.
How is your Korean chess game?
I always win, but it never make me happy.
Why? Is the palace being strange?
As my life in a palace has been 30 years long, it's like looking inside of my hand.
But I still don't know what is right and what is wrong.
You're really...in the main room the mother-in-law is always right
and in the kitchen the wife is always right.
When I first came to the palace, I put
my manhood in a pot with all common sense.
In this place right or wrong don't matter.
but power and powerless matter.
Wait a second.  Did I just say this awesome phrase?
Aren't I something?
You are something.
What would you have wanted to become
if you hadn't become a eunuch?
As for me, all I wanted was to meet a pretty girl
and have babies. Just a happy family.
Let's stop there.  How can I get outside of palace before I die?
You jerk, are you testing to see if your eyeballs will ever pop out?
I really don't like that jerk.
***  King piece hanging on the edge ***
For whom do you think Left Minister and Boo-won were acting treasonous?
You must remove the queen and the young prince from the palace.
Queen Mother.  You must punish the late king's survivors
so that there won't be any problem in the future.
His Majesty must not be coming again today.
Queen Mother, you must make a decision.
Please make a decision.
Don't keep telling me to make decision.
Rather, you need to bring me a solution to persuade His Majesty.
Leave now.
Your Majesty, please get remove the queen and
the young prince from the palace.
Bring me Yoon Minister.
Why can you not look at me?
I'm too embarrass to look at you because you are not dressed properly.
Are you really embarrass?
In my eyes, making your demands while showing
your full intention is more embarrassing.
I'm going to ask you one thing.
As a great King, what is most important?
To practice virtue with empathy.
Then, what is the start of empathy?
um...It's a quality of feeling the pain of those in trouble.
So, having to rid of a woman who
lost her father demonstrates empathy?
Is that the quality of a great King?
However, you must think of the good of the nation
even if you must remove some of us.
You old fart!  How long do you think you'll have
access to the Queen Mother's quarters?
If you don't take all your group and leave now,
I will give you what you wish.
Get out of here.
*** Taking the decorations from the head band. ***
His Majesty is entering.
Stay here.
I don't know what this is about but
why don't you return when there is light outside.
I've heard that you are not well.
How can I be fine with having my father's head hanging on a pole?
Is that the reason you are avoiding me?
Do you know how the government is doing now?
Yes, I know it very well.
How happy would those whose are trying to
get rid of me to discover that you are here?
So please don't seek me out again.
How can you be so cruel?
Why do you think I manage to holding on to this position?
As I'm barely holding on, how can you make me so sad?
Instead, be mad at me.
Tell me that I'm a king who took away the young
prince's position and killed your father.
At least shout out that you hate me so.
What is your name?
It's Guum-oak, Your Majesty.
Why? Are you going to take her to bed?
It's not that I can't do that.
Your Highness, why are doing this to me?
Please don't send me off.  I don't want to.
What are you doing?
Your Highness!  Your Highness!
Your Highness!  Please!
Your Highness, I don't want to go!
Are you happy that everything you wanted has come true?
Are you happy that you finally took your revenge?
I thought you came to the palace for me.
Now ... now, what should I do?
If you want to live, if you want to get out of palace,
I will look for a way.
Why? Am I next?
Do you know where I just came back from?
I just came back from seeing your father's head on a poll.
Does she blame me a lot?
She is just very heavy hearted ...
not being able to eat much and ...
Continue.
How does Her Highness look when she goes to bed?
What?
Well ... that's ... she changes her clothes and takes her hair down.
White ... white sleep wear ...
Who takes off her clothes?
I do.
How do you take it off?
It's ... it's just ...
I untie the knot and ...
Do you bathe her as well?
Yes, Your Majesty.
How do you bathe her?
In a nice scented bath tub ... she soaks her body.
Where do you clean her first?
With a nice clean cloth, I clean her arms ...
then I clean her chest and shoulders.
Is she smooth?
Her skin is very smooth.
Continue.
When she rises up, I clean her legs and in between ...
Your majesty.
This is the room you'll be using from now on.
Although His Majesty has given you the right, you haven't got the title yet.
So take care of your body and don't stroll outside.
Yes, Your Highness.
I understand.
This child is going to take care of you.
Now I'll take my leave.
Is there anything you might need?
No I'm fine.  You may leave now.
Yes.
Get out of here.
Is there anyone there?
Your Majesty, thank you so much.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Hey, Guum-oak!
Are you having fun, my prince?
It's sure is a crazy world.
A servant like me becomes a concubine, and superior like you became a eunuch.
Isn't it such fun?
His Majesty is here.
He came on time.
He asked not to let anyone in.
I've heard you got a promotion.
Couldn't you help get him to come to my quarters?
Isn't knowing you from outside of the palace also a fate?
I have forgotten all events from before I came to the palace.
There isn't anything to remember, since you never helped me.
You are above your place now. You must be careful
with your tongue not to cause any misfortune.
I upset your feelings,
not knowing you are in a difficult situation because of me.
No, not at all.  Actually, I haven't been
feeling good regarding the Boo-won incident.
I don't know why the Queen Mother
is being so harsh on me and the young prince.
Your Highness.
I'm so sorry about Boo-won.
How can I dare blame you?
I must be lacking the qualities of a good king.
What are you saying, Your Majesty?
The late king always mentioned that only you know of how to rule.
How can there be an authority over you?
*** speaking of the Queen Mother ***
I just feel pitiful and stifled.
You need to make a decision to take away the Queen's title.
There is no reason to take her title away.
What?
With both wings cut off, if she has an accident,
who would care about the truth?
You don't need to worry about her.
She has survive 30 years in a turbulent palace.
Do you know why she only has one ear?
She heard something she shouldn't.
She is a smart one.
She knows the flow of events better then anyone.
I heard that you went to Soo-yong Queen's quarter.
Do you know anything about poison?
I have a little experience from when I was younger.
How can you carry such an object in the palace?
That will be big trouble.
But to the eyes of ignorant, it's just a stone.
Do you know how to make poison using that?
You need to burn it first.
Prepare it and be ready.
If that mother and a son don't leave the palace willingly,
there is only one other way.
I heard that there is a sale for His Majesty's sleeping quarter decision.
Me?  How could I dare?
Please bring His Majesty to my quarters on the 3rd of next month.
I mustn't.
Who knows?  If I get a prince, you might get a promotion.
Even eating you, frog, isn't giving me energy...
There ...
Being in the pharmacy for 30 years,
I know the need by hearing one's foot steps.
Let's see if there is a place for a son.
Please remove all personal feeling.
Since there isn't a lot of chances, you must make sure of it.
Okay, Okay.
Your breasts aren't even.  Are they?
No, they are.
If so it requires us to use a different medicine.
If they're uneven, you'll have a harder time conceiving a son.
Your breasts aren't even, are they?
They are even.
There, there.  Let's take a look.
I can't tell by just looking.  I must feel them.
I told you they are even.
You are right.  It's a relief.
This one goes in ... is this one for a son?
This one will change from a daughter to a son.
Take it on the 14th day.
On the 14th day, right?
Wait a second.  This one's for a son.
Oh well, she took the one for the daughter.
People's mind are so cunning.
I never thought I could be up,
but once I got up I don't want to get back down.
Isn't that right, Your Highness?
Having His Majesty once made me wonder,
maybe I can become a queen as well.
Don't you know who you are in front of?
You must speak careful.
How dare you tell me what to do? Huh?
Who do you think I will help if I have His Majesty's mind?
Do you think I could hurt you?
I know what you mean.
Okay. What can I help you with?
If I want to stand out, I must decorate myself a little.
With some jewelry ...
You probably know better than me, so help yourself.
When you have a heir to the throne, I might
build a small quarter far away to stay in.
It's my sin that I haven't conceived an heir for you yet.
Your Highness, His Majesty has a bad headache today.
So, he won't be able to come here tonight.
Did he not come knowing that it's a lucky day
that comes around every 4 years?
Yes, he did.
Let's go.  I must go see him since he is ill.
Have you learn how to become a good king?
It is okay to tell me.
Yes, Your Majesty.  It's "myung", "chal", "tong".
Then what is the meaning of "myung"?
Myung is having clear sight and a good ear.
With your eyes, you should see far with clarity.
With your ear, you must hear the needs of your people.
That's right.
You did good. Here ...
Your Majesty, the medicine is getting cold.
I'm not a king. but a tool to produce an heir.
That isn't true.
How can having an heir to the throne be taken lightly?
Shut up.  You drink it.
It would've been better if you became a king instead.
Your Majesty, the Queen Mother is entering.
Do you know which occasion this is?
I'm not just your son but the King of this nation.
Do you think you are a King just because you are sitting on a throne?
You don't join in on cabinet meetings.
You haven't granted me any chance to accomplish anything.
You keep all the power to make any decision.
Now you're asking me to be a scarecrow/puppet.
I would step down without a word after having an
heir to the throne and things become stable.
When would that be?
What?
Why didn't you just take the throne for yourself instead?
I'm sick and tired of having to mate in front of you.
I'm only expected to produce the seed.
It doesn't have to be with the Queen.
Since it's a luck day ...
Let's give a concubine some chance as well.
Who is it?
It's Guum-oak.
*** it really wasn't ***
Let's go.
How dare ...
Your Majesty.
Why do you have this on you?
Your Majesty, that's because ...
I just asked you why you have this on you.
That ... that's because ... because ...
Your Majesty.
There is something I would like to tell you.
Your Majesty should definitely know about this matter.
Why is this in the hand of other person?
Please do not get upset and sit first.
Don't you know how I really feel?
Do you hate me so much?
I ... I'm not as good as that eunuch?
Bring him in.
I thought I recognized him.
Isn't he the one who used to live in the same house?
How can you disguise a man like him to bring him into the palace?
You must speak carefully.
Please explain yourself.
Why is this person here in the palace?
Although he was from the house I grew in,
only after eunuch introduction did I recognize him.
Are you asking me to believe you?
I vividly remember his stare towards you.
Your Highness and this jerk definitely ...
Who's the father to your son -
you weren't pregnant for the whole term?
Is he really my brother's son?
Take his clothes off him.
I need to confirm that he is truly not a man.
Your Majesty, do you need to go that far?
Take his clothes off now!
Your Majesty, why would you want to
see a monstrous thing like that?
Now please take your leave.
Your Highness, don't you know?
Do you think that I really don't know your heart?
As the Queen Mother watches each and every move ...
I don't care about the Queen Mother, or anything else.
Please look at me.
I'm so ashamed.  Why do you think that I continue?
Your Majesty.
You may come back when you truly becomes a King.
I'll become a King.  I will definitely become a King.
What happened last night with
His Majesty is against heavenly rules.
Others should not find out about this.
Yes, Your Highness.
You know the truth ... you know what
I've done to give him the throne.
Get rid of them.
Why ... why didn't you tell me?
*** familiar term speech ***
What would change by telling you?
If you had just told me what happened ...
*** familiar term speech ***
Let's leave.
Leave?  We tried that once before.
*** familiar term speech ***
Instead of living this way, let's just leave everything and just take off.
When we get out of palace, we'll all be murdered.
*** familiar term speech ***
I can't let harm come to the child.
No matter what, he is the prince of the late king.
*** familiar term speech ***
You will die because of that one reason.
No ... No matter what, I will protect him myself.
***  familiar term speech ***
What ... what shall I do?
*** familiar term speech ***
What would you like me to do for you?
Your Majesty, that is the 40th arrow already.  Your health ...
You asked for me, Your Majesty.
Take a shot.
I want to see your skill.
How could I dare to hold your bow?
Give him an arrow.
Kwon-yoo.
What reason did you have to hide your
identity and came into the palace?
I've became a eunuch because it was only way
a man without manhood can succeed.
How dare a person like you had feelings toward a royal concubine?
Feelings? No, there couldn't be such an emotion.
I must go to the Queen's quarters.  As I made
a big mistake yesterday, I must apologize.
Instead ...The Queen Mother is still waiting for your morning visit ...
He's still suspicious of the matter.
You can't live this way forever.
Your Majesty, you shouldn't be doing this.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, what are you doing?
Kwon-yoo ... where is Kwon-yoo?
Call for him.
I will no longer take medicine like that.
But Your Majesty,
the Queen Mother checks on your medicine everyday ...
Then you take it.
What? For me, trying to suppress the male hormone, I don't even
consume Kimchi with garlic.  How can I take this type of medicine?
Oh ... does a man without manhood have a sex drive?
I'm sorry to say, but having no ejaculation
doesn't mean that there is no sex drive.
Kwon-yoo ... you drink it.
Why? You can't drink it?  Are you worry about having a sex drive?
Drink it up.
I can't let my child be in danger.
No matter what, I will protect him.
Since you don't even have the root of it,
there is nothing to worry about.
What is wrong? How can this be?
Who is it? Who ordered this?
Please calm down, Your Majesty.
I don't know anything ... as on any other day,
I got the ingredient and made the medicine myself ...
Your Majesty.
I will killed anyone who speaks of this news.
Call in a doctor secretly.  Save this jerk.
I have to hear something from him.
Please spare my life, Your Majesty.
I really don't know anything about this.
Bring in the evidence.
Do you know what this is?  This came out of your room.
I really don't know anything.
Did the Queen Mother ask you to get rid of me?
That didn't happen, Your Majesty.
Then who takes care of all the ingredients?
You shall not deny that knowledge.
It's Yoon-jungho Minister.
His Majesty ordered that no one be let in.
Here.  Here.
Here, come out of it.
Water ... water.
Here you go.
M ... more.
Are you okay now?
I'm like a pumpkin leaf that got hammered by hail.
I must look terrible.
This is not too bad.
He revealed the Yoon Minister's name.
Soon there will be blood all over the palace.
So, let me go first.
What do you mean?
You know better than anyone, what power does to people.
His Majesty probably wants to use this
latest event to solve his own agenda.
They say even rolling on a field full of dog poop is
better than dead. I don't want to live like this any longer.
I can't do it.
If the King want your name as well, what would you do?
What are you doing?
I will take you outside of the palace.
It's no use.  I'm already too tired.
I told you I will take care of everything.
Hey ... Thanks for not making me so lonely.
I'm sorry that I go first.
Put that down.  Please put it down.
Stay alive.
Phil-il, you ...
Please don't wonder around as you go off.
Just head towards ... just head toward the light.
I will bring the prince back safely.
I will see you soon so - don't worry.
Mother, I don't want to leave.
Mother. Mother.
Are you sure you are not telling a lie?
How dare I tell a lie to you, Your Highness.
She passed the eunuch's son off as heir to the king.
She got the queen's position with a lie?
How dare she ...
Is there someone out there?
Yes, Your Highness.
Take her to the secret palace.
M ... me?
Your Highness. I would rather become a servant again.
Just don't send me to the secret palace.
Instead of going to the secret palace, I would rather die!
Kill her.
Your ... Your highness!  No, Your Highness ... Your Highness!
Your Highness!  Let go! Let go! Your Highness.
Why are you doing this to me? Your Highness!
Your Highness, please save me. Your Highness!
Let go! Please save me! I don't want to die!
I'm sorry!
We have an order to bring you from the Queen Mother herself.
Yoon-jungho Minister come out and receive the order of the King.
You jerk. How dare you come into this quarter?
What are you doing?
It's your King's order to arrest Yoon-jungho minister as a traitor.
What treason? Get out of here.
I'm sorry Your Highness.
The King has ordered his imprisonment right away.
The King's order?
Who do you think gave you that position?
How dare you aim a sword towards me?
You dare to aim a sword toward me.
I'll go see His Majesty,
so go take care of the bitch in the secret palace.
Your Majesty, the head eunuch has arrived.
Your majesty.
Where are you, Your Majesty?
I came knowing that you're here.
Come out here, Your Majesty.
Since I got up here and look down,
I understand why you like it up here.
What are you doing there?
For what reason did you have
Yoon-jungho Minister put in prison?
I heard that you pushed back the soldiers I sent.
How dare you send soldiers to your own mother?
I must be a puppet King.
How much did you like that place?
Cutting off my four limbs and making me a puppet.
Now you are trying to get rid of me?
What are you talking about?
Did you order me to be poisoned?
Your Majesty.
The royal doctor has already confessed everything.
You conspireed with Yoon-jungho Minister and tried to kill me?
What? You are speaking nonsense ...
Right?  I also couldn't understand it.
Your man, Yoon-jungho Minister,
couldn't have conspire by himself.
This is slander.
This must be Soo-yong Queen's doing.
That bitch, I will just ...
Oh ... ok.  I understand it all now.
Make her the villain by putting poison in the medicine.
Kill me, then kill Soo-yong Queen and the young prince as well.
Who were you going to use to fill this empty space?
What are you saying?
The Yoon-jungho Minister and I have lived to put you on the throne.
Truly, you have lasted a long time.
Kill her.
Yes sir.
Who are you people?
Go away!  Kill them all.
Do not spare any of the traitors.  Kill them all.
Yes sir.
Do you know what a bitch Soo-yong Queen is?
The late king could not have a child.
Can't you tell the truth for once?
Did you already forget?  Your King died after the birth as well.
After that, I used the medicine on the late king.
Although I was suspicious of the pregnancy.
Po ... poison.  Did you use the poison on him?
Who told you to do such an act?
For whom ... For whom did you do such an act?
When did I ever tell you that I wanted to be the King?
When did I ever tell you I wanted to be the King?!
Baby.  Look at me.
I'm the mother who protected you from this turbulent palace.
Why did you make me a King,
and turn me into a person who can't trust you.
Can you not trust your own mother?
Truly, will you go against your mother's will?
When we face them we shall find the truth.
Is there anyone outside?
Bring in Yoon-jungho Minister and Kwon-yoo.
That won't happen.
I will make sure that it happens.
Yoon Minister.
As the head eunuch, I've followed your orders
and brought the wrongdoers.
This person has confessed the truth.
Also, the proof was  found in his quarters.
Who do you think the royal doctor identified
as the source of the poison?
How should I know that?
Why can't you say it?
I know nothing about the matter.
Aren't I the one who drank the medicine?
Then you want me to ask you why you hesitated
when I ask you to drink the medicine?
Aren't I the one who drank the medicine?
Then you want me to ask you why you hesitated
when I ask you to drink the medicine?
You already knew about the poison in the medicine.
Your Majesty.
That's enough.
I'm the one who is asking this eunuch.
You definitely knew about it.
How did you know about the poison in the medicine?
Your Majesty, don't you know what a bitch Soo-yong Queen is?
That eunuch and the bitch conspire together
to ruin the kingdom together ...
You need to bring her in to confess right now.
That's right.
I am the wrongdoer.
I have wronged by conceiving a prince
by the late King, as well as by being alive.
You have indeed.  Using a prince to ruin this kingdom
is indeed a wrong doing.
Also, troubling your king by being alive is wrong doing.
However Your Majesty, who is that person? He is the underling
of the one who's responsible for my father's death.
How can anyone in this world conspire together
with the person who's responsible for your father's death.
You bitch.  How dare you show fake tears?!
What would a little one know and what could he possibly do?
How can I be ambitions for your position?
I would rather choose death by biting my own tongue.
However, I could not die with a misunderstanding.
Tell the truth with your own tongue.
Who ordered you to put poison in the medicine?
The Queen Mother asked me to make the poison.
With that poison Yoon-jungho Minister has ...
This is slander.
Your Majesty.
What are you doing?
Why did you do it?
You wanted this throne so much you wanted to kill me for it?!
Tell me.
You must calm down.
The Queen Mother is losing breath.
Your Majesty.
Except him, take the others and kill them all.
As for the Queen Mother, do not let her out of her quarters.
If there is anyone who tries to contact her,
I will punish them with the most severe punishment.
Your Majesty. Your Majesty.  I'm innocent, Your Majesty.
Thank you for keeping your promise.
I will always remember your good deed.
Please protect our child.
Our child?
The Prince is no one's child.  He is my child.
When you become a real King ... you may come back.
Is is all done now?
Would you take me now?
The King has passed. The King has passed.  The King has passed.
... You must control your own mind in order to put
your best effort into the care for the well of the nation.
Do you understand me?
Your Highness.
Has it actually happened?
I'm so sorry, Your Highness.
Then, you came to fetch me.
I have a favor to ask you.