WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
My fellow Americans,
no hacker should be able to
shut down our networks...
A massive attack.
Data is inaccessible.
Or invade the privacy
of American families.
You're being watched and recorded.
I urge this Congress
to protect our children's information.
Dear brothers and sisters,
now is the time to open your eyes.
I started intercepting all
the traffic on your network.
That's when I noticed something strange.
That's when I decided to hack you.
We are fsociety!
We are finally free!
We are on the verge
of taking down this virtual reality.
Exciting time in the world
right now, exciting time.
So this is what a revolution looks like.
Why did you do it?
I wanted to save the world.
"Mr. Robot,"
USA's Golden Globe
and Peabody award-winning original drama
about a vigilante hacker with
a mission to change the world
has engaged audiences
like no other show.
"Mr. Robot" won two Golden Globes,
three Critics' Choice Awards,
but what really says something
about "Mr. Robot" is
fans found this show even
before the critics showed up,
even before the awards showed up.
Its realistic portrayal
of a world where
information is vulnerable,
everyone is being watched, and
anyone can be compromised
has fueled its rise as
a cultural phenomenon.
"Mr. Robot" comes at a time
where you can't turn on the television
or read a newspaper without hearing
about some massive corporate
or government hack.
But how much of the world
portrayed by "Mr. Robot" is possible?
A lot more than you might think.
Over the next hour, we'll examine
what's truly at risk in our
technology-obsessed world.
The only completely secure computer
is a computer that no one can use.
We'll talk
to the creator and cast
as well as pop culture experts
about why "Mr. Robot" has
resonated so powerfully.
Something incredibly prophetic
happened on the show,
almost, you know, weeks away
from it happening in real life.
And through
unprecedented access
to cybersecurity experts
and real-life hackers,
we'll reveal how "Mr. Robot" is
mirroring real-world scenarios
if not outright predicting them.
You look at the hacks that
played out in season one...
gaining access to Steel Mountain,
bumping next to someone
to steal and clone
their proximity badge,
getting a backdoor in a phone...
all of those are hacks that
we read about in the news
every week now.
Plus, we'll also discuss
what's in store for season two.
The second season... it's very
different from season one.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
And the Golden Globe goes to...
"Mr. Robot." Yep.
"Mr. Robot"
is the brainchild
of creator Sam Esmail.
"Mr. Robot" is about this
sort of modern society
and the way we're so
dependent on technology
just to even socialize,
so it's really about this
guy who cannot connect,
and the only way he does
so is by hacking people.
"Mr. Robot" tells
the story of Elliot Alderson.
By night, he's a socially withdrawn
but gifted computer hacker
who uses his skills
to expose the misdeeds of others.
Wait, hold on. I'll give you the money.
I'll pay you.
How much do you want? I'll pay you.
That's the part you were
wrong about, Rohit.
I don't give a shit about money.
By day, he's
a cybersecurity expert
who's been recruited by
the mysterious Mr. Robot
to bring down the very corporation
he was hired to protect.
What if you could take
down one conglomerate,
a conglomerate so deeply entrenched
in the world's economy
that "too big to fail"
doesn't even come close
to describing it?
Together, with
the hacker group fsociety,
he succeeds in crippling the
world's most powerful firm,
setting in motion a global crisis
beyond anyone's control.
Evil Corp, the people of the world
who have been enslaved
by you have been freed.
Your financial data has been destroyed.
"Mr. Robot" features
a stellar ensemble cast
led by the Critics' Choice
Award winner for Best Actor,
Rami Malek.
Getting in Elliot's head,
as odd as it seems,
is, you know, something I really enjoy,
you know, to go into his psychosis,
what he's suffering through,
the good in him, the bad, the ugly.
All of it is... it's
something that consumes me.
Christian Slater,
winner of the Golden Globe Award
for Best Supporting Actor, plays Mr.
Robot.
The relationship between Mr.
Robot and Elliot...
you know, this character, Mr. Robot,
comes into his life and
lures him into his world
to become part of this team of people
that are really looking
to change society.
I tried to protect you, son,
but they caught up to us.
What are you talking about?
That's Darlene and Angela.
Elliot, who are you talking to?
What do you mean? I'm talking to...
This dark and edgy series,
with its cinematic style and
unpredictable plotlines,
has struck a chord with viewers.
The world of hacking really
is sort of an obscure world
to the general population,
so the fact that we broke
out in any way like that
is incredibly shocking.
Kate Coyne,
executive editor at "People,"
and Emily Yoshida,
entertainment editor at "The Verge,"
have closely followed "Mr. Robot's" rise
to prominence in pop culture.
I think "Mr. Robot"
made such an impression
because of the timeliness.
It's inspired big debates
that went beyond the events of the show.
I think that's always the sign of a show
that is meaningful for the
time in which it's being made.
The things that concern us,
the big ideas that concern
us at any given era...
I think "Mr. Robot"
really taps into that.
This is very much a show
that could only exist
in a post-WikiLeaks world.
You know, everybody, I think,
probably suspects that, on some level,
what they're doing is being
watched or recorded.
When a cry goes up about the NSA
or about Edward Snowden or something,
a lot of people practically
just shrug, like,
"Yeah, yeah, probably...
you're probably listening
to my cell calls."
That's crazy, but that's the
state that we're in now.
Anybody can hack into anything.
His was the easiest to hack.
Password was 123456Seven.
I witnessed his first "I love you"
with Angela over Gchat.
Then I witnessed the first
of many infidelities
with Stella B.
Everything about us is all digital.
It's all in a cloud.
Now you can go get somebody's
social security, fingerprints,
images, everything.
You can literally take
over their entire life.
That's frightening.
It's not like they're talking about it
in science-fiction terms.
What they're tackling is something
that's actually currently,
right now happening.
Coming up on "Mr.
Robot dec0d3d,"
we'll take a deeper look at the
rise of hacking culture...
There's always been a little bit
of wish fulfillment to hacker stories
in that they are the sort
of modern superheroes.
And learn
how a Hollywood movie
alerted a president to the
dangers of cybersecurity.
Plus, we'll also discuss
what's in store for season two.
But first, a word from
our corporate overlords!
Come on, kid. We got
big things in store.
Big things.
"Mr. Robot's"
authentic portrayal
of computer hacking has alerted us
to the real-world dangers we all face.
Now we'll find out just
how much we're at risk.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
How about Global Thermonuclear War?
In 1983,
the movie "WarGames"
forever changed the way
we would look at hacking.
Ronald Reagan was apparently
shown the movie "WarGames,"
and he commissioned, you
know, a study as to:
Is this actually possible?
And everybody was
expecting the answer was,
"No, you can't start, you know,
a global thermonuclear war
"just by dialing up, you know,
a computer accidentally
and getting it to talk to you."
And unfortunately, the
answer came back going,
"Well, um, this is a little
more possible than we thought."
"WarGames" also spawned
a whole new generation of hackers.
I mean, I remember being a kid
and watching Matthew Broderick
do all that and going,
"That's really cool.
That's really awesome," you know?
And, by the way, he saved the world.
It's the first time that you
saw Hollywood trying to depict
what people could do with computers
that went beyond just playing
games and sending emails
and got me even more excited in
computers and computer hacking.
What is hacking? Who hacks?
How and why is it executed?
To get the answers, we went
to world-renowned specialists
in the field of cybersecurity
and to the foremost
experts on the subject,
the hackers themselves.
Everybody has a different answer
on what a hacker is or what
is a hack, but for me,
it comes down to making
technology do stuff
it was never meant to do.
The show "Mr. Robot"
I'm particular fond of
because they point out how, oftentimes,
it's very simplistic,
the hacking mechanism.
Sometimes it's having physical access,
so you can swap a SIM out in a phone.
Other times, it's social engineering.
It's not that they cracked
some code or some encryption.
It's that they sent an email,
and they misrepresented
who they were, they...
and got you to click on an attachment
and run the code for them
or that they called up on the phone
and pretended that they were,
you know, a technical person
to get you to give information.
Hello?
Hi, this is Sam from Bank of
E security fraud department.
Unfortunately, I have to inform you
that your account's been compromised.
What? What happened?
First, before I can
answer any questions,
I need to verify some information.
Are you still at 306 Hawthorne Avenue?
Yes, apartment 2C.
Great, and your security question,
favorite baseball team.
Um, Yankees.
I don't remember this being
a security question.
And lastly, your pet's name.
Um, Flipper. Uh, who am I speaking to?
Can I get your name and numb...
With those details plus a
dictionary brute-force attack,
it'll take my program maybe two minutes
to crack his password.
The last five, ten years,
hacking has become like a new superpower
that hasn't been invented,
and because of everyone's
reliance on technology
and all your personal
information being online,
this power just sort of came about.
Hacking her was simple.
Her password: Dylan 2791.
Favorite artist
and the year in which she
was born, backwards.
People are horrible at being
sources of randomness,
so, you know, somebody might think,
"Oh, I used my dog's
name, my baby's name,
and the birth... and the birth date."
That's a horrible password.
It might seem complicated to you,
but we know how you think
because you're a human,
and humans are predictable.
This doesn't make sense.
Did he know I was gonna hack him?
Did he let me?
I'm gonna need to wipe everything.
"Hackers," you know, it
used to be a nasty word.
It was, like, synonymous
with "criminal,"
but now they're part of the system.
But not all hackers
are cut from the same cloth.
So a white hat hacker is one
who would be hired by a corporation
to hack their systems
for the sole purpose
of finding the flaws,
whereas black hat... there's
no permission whatsoever,
and it's usually for malicious purposes.
And then there's the middle ground,
which is grey hat.
Hello, Evil Corp. We are fsociety.
Over the years, we've been watching you:
your financial abuse of the poor,
your corruption of governments,
your cover-ups of the murder
of innocent ordinary citizens
all for the sake of profit.
This is why we at fsociety
have decided you must die.
I would characterize the
members of fsociety
as probably falling into that grey area
because, while their
intentions are good,
they are doing highly illegal things.
The entire company's gonna be reeling
from all the data dumps we've
got in store for them,
and, man, do we have some goodies.
Some good old-fashioned
executive racism,
sexism, fascism.
Trust me... we are gonna
"ism" so much all over them,
they won't be able to see straight.
Unlike their motives,
there are many psychological
traits that hackers share.
Elliot, he's probably
depicted more accurate
than I've seen in a long time,
not just for the technical capabilities
and how it is but the actual,
like, psychological profile.
He's got that young hacker vibe.
And then his involvement in
how he feels about society
and that counter culture I
think is very accurate.
I hate when I can't
hold in my loneliness.
This crying's been happening too often,
every other week now.
What do normal people do
when they get this sad?
He's such a complicated character.
He's full of contradictions.
He hates what society has become,
but he also wants to save it.
He looks down on the people
that he cares about,
but then he also protects them.
His abandonment issues
are actually something
that I believe personally
and I've seen in my work.
I think it is a big motivator
on why people get into hacking.
Elliot's, you know, trapped in a bubble.
He's very lonely. He doesn't know how
to connect with people, so
he hacks into their lives.
I think all of us to a certain degree
can connect with that
type of loneliness,
and the need to maybe not be so robotic
and have more of a human
connection with one another.
I like you, bro,
and I want you to like me too.
Am I crazy not to like this guy?
Amongst some of his Facebook likes
are George W. Bush's "Decision Points,"
"Transformers 2: Revenge of the Fallen,"
and the music of Josh Groban.
Must I really justify
myself any further?
When you're socially awkward,
or you're worried about
people judging you,
you have all these anxieties
that just aren't there
when you're in front of a computer.
It's a lot harder to talk to people
than it is to deal with
a piece of software.
But when
hackers do come together
and groups are formed, leaders emerge.
You want to talk about reality?
We haven't lived in anything
remotely close to it
since the turn of the century.
We turned it off, took
out the batteries,
snacked on a bag of GMOs
while we tossed the remnants
in the ever-expanding dumpster
of the human condition.
We live in branded houses,
trademarked by corporations,
built on bipolar numbers.
In every hacker group
there's this leader that,
online they're quiet,
they're hidden in the background,
but when you meet them they're
actually really extroverted
and, like, passionate and principled.
I didn't want to hurt you, Romero.
I just wanted you to come
back to the arcade with me
so we could change the world together.
It is this
instigator mentality
that forms the basis of Mr.
Robot's character.
Do I think Elliot needs Mr. Robot?
I think he's a vital element
to Elliot's survival.
He is that darker side that
will sometimes do things
that Elliot otherwise would
be incapable of doing.
Coming up, we'll
explore the eerie ways
"Mr. Robot" parallels the real world.
The Sony hack got a lot of notoriety.
The Ashley Madison hack
got a lot of notoriety.
Our show is getting a lot of notoriety
because of the real world connections.
Plus, we'll also discuss
what's in store for season two.
We kind of, like, press the
gas pedal down really hard.
Gotten to know my stunt
double more this season,
so that might say something.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
"Mr. Robot's"
authentic portrayal
of computer hacking has alerted us
to the real-world dangers we all face.
Now we'll find out just
how much we're at risk.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
This kid should not be
allowed to do what he did.
He hacked into my private life.
And then those Ashley
Madison dumps happened.
My wife found out about
everything anyway.
She left me.
In a year
in which we've seen
a record number of cyber attacks,
"Mr. Robot's" timeliness
is almost uncanny.
I don't know that a TV show
can necessarily predict the future,
but certainly, they can hold a mirror up
to the direction in which we're headed.
And while some storylines
are ripped from the headlines,
other times, "Mr.
Robot" was there first.
There were two instances on "Mr. Robot"
where something incredibly
prophetic happened on the show
weeks away from it
happening in real life.
The Ashley Madison hacks were one.
You know, one of the escorts was 15.
And then the other one was the
shooting of the news anchor
in Virginia that happened
so close to a similar event
happening on "Mr. Robot"
that the finale had to be delayed a week
just out of sensitivity.
These aren't just isolated incidences
that exist in a bubble.
These are things that are
symptoms of larger things
going on in our society.
Colby either used hacking groups
or worked in conjunction with them.
I think a lot of "Mr.
Robot" and the hacks in it
kind of reflect reality.
It's happening, it's happening,
it's happening, it's happening.
The hacks that are happening
every week in the real world
are stranger than fiction almost.
Power plants hacked,
a movie not released because
North Korea was upset,
some of the biggest
retailers in the world
lose millions and millions
worth of credit cards or data,
hospitals shut down because
all their files got encrypted
by someone trying to get
ransom out of them.
These all sound like the storylines
of a TV show about hacking,
but it's actually happening now.
"Secretary of Homeland
Security Jeh Johnson
"released a statement today
stating that these groups
"lack the resources and
knowledge of the USL
to successfully mount
an attack," end quote.
There are some brilliant
people out there,
both on the offense and
defensive side of things
that can do amazing
things with computers.
You got this, you got
this, you got this.
And it's both inspiring
and kind of scary
sometimes to see that.
I, uh... I have to go. I'm sorry.
I need to go to my office.
What'd you do?
I spoofed a text
from her husband.
So, yeah, probably the most
alarming hack we've seen
was the Sony hack where
not only, you know,
all of these email
archives were compromised,
but also it was released
on a schedule of,
you know, every week we're gonna
have another one of these,
until you meet with our demands.
Another parallel
between "Mr. Robot"
and the real world can be seen
in fsociety's threatened use
of a data dump, a scenario
inspired by the Sony hack.
They hit the mother
lode during the breach,
potentially terabytes
worth of email and files.
They're threatening to dump everything.
They released the video this morning.
Meet our demands and we will
consider not destroying you.
Consider yourself warned.
This is, you know, a way
to hold power accountable.
It can also be used to
harass and to silence
and really as an instrument of fear.
In an age where
everyone is connected,
and privacy is becoming
harder to protect,
"Mr. Robot" has shined a light
on the risks and the realities
we all face every day.
The writers have tapped
into the paranoia
that we all now feel,
that all of our information
is just ripe for the taking.
He got into my system, and he
wants me to the put the CD
on one of the computers at work.
Why does he want to do that?
I don't know, Stella.
He didn't give me a full explanation.
So he's got naked pics of me?
Is that the only thing you're seriously
taking away from this conversation?
Hey, babe.
"Mr. Robot" is absolutely
showing everyone
that we are living in
a society right now
in which secrets just don't exist.
You maybe can't trust
many people at all.
I know she went through a
divorce four years ago.
I know she was devastated by it
and has been dating losers
on eHarmony ever since.
The more accessible we make ourselves,
the more people are
probably going to be able
to take advantage of that.
By the end of watching
season one of "Mr. Robot,"
anyone who previously just
typed away on a computer,
you're probably going about
those transactions now
with just a little more caution,
a little bit more of a realization
that that little lock symbol
doesn't mean a whole lot.
Our personal
information, our very identity,
is accessible to anyone, any time,
and we look to the
government to protect us
from criminal activity,
but a recent case between
Apple and the FBI,
who are trying to unlock a
terrorist's cell phone,
brings up a gray area.
Should the government be given access
to your personal devices?
Telecommunications companies
have been cooperating
with law enforcement and
intelligence agencies
for nearly a century.
And so you have the FBI saying
"Oh, we can't hack into your iPhone.
We need your help in doing it."
And Apple is saying,
"Our stuff is so secure,
it's a danger to everybody
if we help you out on this."
NSA and the intelligence
community in general
is focused on getting
intelligence wherever it can,
by any means possible, so
while they may be intending
to target someone associated
with a foreign government,
or someone that they
suspect of terrorism,
they're collecting your
communications to do so.
You would ask any person on the street,
"Should the government be
able to hack into a phone
to investigate a terrorism suspect?"
and everybody would say yes.
And then, you ask them,
"Well, should they be able
to hack into your phone?"
and everybody would say no.
We have to look really, really hard
at the kind of slippery
slopes that we're building,
as far as how much access the government
or any other corporation
has into our data.
Any analyst at any time
can target anyone,
from you or your accountant
to a federal judge
to even the president, if
I had a personal email.
Ben Franklin said it best:
"Those who give up liberty
for security will have neither."
: Coming up: from
the tech to the techniques,
see how "Mr. Robot" is
as real as it gets.
Every single hack that we
show on the show is possible.
Plus, we'll show you
what's in store for season two.
Our infinite loop of insanity.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
"Mr. Robot's"
authentic portrayal
of computer hacking has alerted us to
the real-world dangers we all face.
Now we'll find out just
how much we're at risk.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
Maybe we should consider rehab.
I'm not a junkie.
Then you'll need to prove it to me.
Submit to a bi-monthly
drug test, voluntarily.
That's the only way that
I'll recommend your release.
This is William Highsmith.
He's not only the head of
the IT department here,
he's also an idiot.
He uses useless virus
scans, dated servers,
and security software
that runs on Windows 98.
One of the reasons why I made this place
my primary care facility.
I can make my health records look like
every other obedient zombie out there.
"Mr. Robot's" popularity
with many of its most fervent fans
can largely be attributed
to its realistic portrayal
of computer technology.
That's the purview of technical
consultant Kor Adana.
I'm involved in every aspect
of all the tech that
you see on the show.
I'm involved in pitching
the ideas of the hacks
that we see fsociety being a part of.
It's not your typical
tech consulting gig.
Too many movies or TV shows
try to make hacking just magic,
and they don't explain it.
It's just something that
you can't understand,
and because of that,
it's some superpower.
I think one of the greatest
compliments we can get
is just how realistic and
authentic the show actually
portrays what's really
going on out there.
One of the things that's
so great about the show
is that you'll actually
learn a few things.
This is bad, worst DDoS
attack I've ever seen.
DDoS attacks are a bunch of
hackers getting together
to overload a system to
take it down for, you know,
a temporary amount of time.
It's a flood of traffic.
We're sending signals over wires,
and if you have too many
signals at the same time,
the real signal can't get through.
Tried to reboot the servers, but
they're not coming back up.
Dude, someone is straight
up finger blasting
their entire network right now.
I've learned quite a
bit, maybe too much.
It's kind of scary, mm, what
I'm capable of these days.
For the
creators and fans alike,
there's an appreciation that the realism
lies in the details.
People are screen-capturing the images
on the computer screens,
and looking at them to
see if they're real.
And they are real, and
that takes a lot of time.
One screenshot that was shown, I think,
for less than a second took
somebody over ten hours of work
to make that an authentic
load-up sequence.
All of the screens are
designed, essentially, by me,
and I work with animators
to achieve those
and make sure that they're
technically accurate.
I think details like that
really enriches and deepens the world.
It makes the show this
almost alternate reality
that's not too detached from our own.
More than just imagery,
"Mr. Robot's" realism extends
to the schemes and methods
that are currently in use
by the hacking community.
Their ability to infiltrate and
alter a physical environment
was illustrated by the
Steel Mountain hack,
a scenario that closely paralleled
one of history's most famous
cyber attacks, Stuxnet.
The US and Israel had a joint operation
where they created an
amazingly complex program
that hacked into the computers
controlling the speed with which
centrifuges were spinning
in the plant in Iran
that was enriching uranium.
And about half of Iran's
centrifuges were destroyed.
It probably slowed down their
nuclear program by three years.
To think about the steps
that are required
to plan that and then
causing kinetic damage,
is incredible.
He wants to hack Steel Mountain's
climate control system,
raise the facility's heat high enough
to destroy all the tapes.
And you think sticking
this behind the thermostat
will do all that?
From a authenticity standpoint,
if you wanted to hack
a major corporation,
they would have off-site tape backups
at a location like Steel Mountain.
There. Deep in the Adirondacks.
In 145-plus acre former limestone mine.
3-ton steel gates, 24/7 armed guards,
closed circuit cameras, NOC staffing.
A fair amount of the plots
and techniques and the hacks
and the approaches in "Mr. Robot"
are actually plausible.
The reason they're plausible:
it's 90% preparation
and only 10% execution.
There's a fair amount
of understanding how
the other systems and the targets
that you're focusing on work,
and then having your, you know,
system and your hack ready
so that you can execute it, you
know, when the time is right.
All we need is one security flaw.
Look at this place, man. It
was built not to have any.
I see about... six walking around.
Social engineering
is one example of
a real-world hacking method,
and "Mr. Robot" illustrates
it to perfection.
The social engineering
component of hacking, I think,
is one of the most
important aspects of it.
Taking advantage of that
human element of security.
Bill Harper is our first exploit.
He isn't gonna give the
search much scrutiny.
He'll get us to Level 1,
but Bill is not gonna be
able to get us to Level 2.
And we need to get to Level 2.
You're gonna ask to speak
to his supervisor, Wendy.
She'll get us to exactly
where we need to be.
Then we'll be able to get
rid of her from the van.
After that, you connect the Raspberry Pi
to the climate control system,
and Bob's your uncle.
It doesn't matter how
hardened your system is,
how great your security policies are,
what kind of software you
have on your system.
There's always gonna be a human
that has access to information
that's important.
And you can always find a way
to manipulate that person.
People are all just people, right?
When it gets down to it,
everyone's the same.
They love something.
They want something.
They fear something.
Specifics help, but
specifics don't change
the way that everyone is vulnerable.
It just changes the way that we
access those vulnerabilities.
Great example of this is
Elliot impersonating a
multi-million-dollar CEO
to get through the door.
I really think you should look me up.
It... it just doesn't work like that.
I'm sorry, sir.
You impersonate someone
that is in need of
some kind of help or assistance,
most of the time, they'll
want to help you.
Mr. Sepiol?
Mr. Sepiol!
I have some good news.
And that's why Bill Harper
is a perfect exploit,
desperate enough for the
business to break protocol
and let me in.
Lonely enough to break.
They won't even know
that they're giving you
some kind of information
that will help you
hack their system later.
But it happens all the time.
Coming up on "Mr.
Robot dec0d3d,"
we delve into the ethics of hacktivism.
If you feel that there is injustice,
sometimes the only way to deal with it
is to out-monster the monster.
Plus, we'll also discuss
what's in store for season two.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
"Mr. Robot's"
authentic portrayal
of computer hacking has alerted us to
the real-world dangers we all face.
Now, we'll find out just
how much we're at risk.
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
You're blowing up a gas pipeline.
The world is a dangerous place, Elliot.
Not because of those who do evil,
but because of those who
look on and do nothing.
This is war. People will die.
C'est la mort.
I'm not killing anyone.
Tell me one thing, Elliot.
Are you a one or a zero?
That's the question you
have to ask yourself.
Are you a yes or a no?
Are you gonna act or not?
Hacktivism is the act of
compromising a computer system
or a network with a
political agenda in mind.
One of the reasons for "Mr.
Robot's" huge success
is that it speaks to the
current generation's
distrust of our corporate culture
and to their frustration
with the status quo.
But is taking matters into our
own hands ever justified?
In many cases, hacktivism
takes the form of
anti-establishment points of view.
The governments of the world
and their corporate masters
do not want us to speak. Why?
Because we unlock truths.
We expose villains.
If you have any interest in
waking from your slumber
and retrieving lost,
damaged, or stolen memory,
we are here for you.
We have your back.
We are fsociety.
A lot of fsociety and
the mask is obviously
evocative of Anonymous
and the Guy Fawkes mask
that a lot of people in
Anonymous started to wear
back when they had
their campaign against
the Church of Scientology.
Their declaration of war on Scientology
definitely served as an inspiration
for some of the content that
you see on "Mr. Robot."
Corporate greed is a trickle-down desire
that reaches even the
bottom of the food chain.
And for what? Wealth? Power?
What the shit?
It's a pathetic fable,
and you, Allsafe, are a defender of...
Holy shit. fsociety knows us.
But your sweet dream is over
and your nightmare is about to begin.
Gideon Goddard, you are a lackey
to your corporate overlords...
Someone shut this off.
Serving them, slave to master.
We are exposing your role to your world,
and the world is very angry.
I have a very anti-corporate,
anti-establishment spirit
in me, and as much as I
appreciate Occupy Wall Street,
I think as an adult I
want to use that anger
to actually do something
constructive and positive.
And I think, like, for
example, the Arab Spring
is a good example where
they really kind of got empowered
through social media, actually,
through technology,
and really made change.
The Arab Spring is a
really good example of
security in action.
If you're an activist in Bahrain,
you need your email, you
need your Facebook account
to be secure, because if the government,
which controls all the
Internet infrastructure,
can get in, that's it, you're done.
They're gonna take... come to your house
and put a bag over your head
and no one will ever see you again.
Now whatever it is you
think you're doing
freeing the world, freeing the masses,
the guys I work for,
they ain't motivated by
"Kumbaya" shit like that.
Right and wrong is relative,
and it comes down to your own ideology,
your own moral compass,
and whether or not you feel
passionate enough about that
to act on it.
How come I'm not in trouble?
Even though what you did was wrong,
you're still a good kid.
And that guy was a prick.
Sometimes that matters more.
I think the reason it
thematically resonates
with people when you're watching
a show like "Mr. Robot,"
if the antagonist is strong enough
or if you feel that there is injustice
coming from the antagonist,
if there's an injustice in the world...
sometimes the only way to deal with it
is to out-monster the monster.
Fernando Vera, Shayla's supplier
and one of the worst human
beings I've ever hacked.
He does all his drug transactions
through emails, IMs, Twitter.
He can't be allowed to exist anymore.
When you break down
motivations of hackers,
it's money, ideology, coercion, ego,
or revenge, and sometimes
criss and cross.
In "Mr. Robot,"
Elliot's ideology is founded on
his desire to avenge his father's death.
This isn't even about my revolution.
This is more than that for you.
This is about how those bastards
slowly killed your father
and how you wished he'd
done something about it,
but he didn't
because he was a zero,
just like you're being right now.
It's just a basic question of, you know,
when does the good outweigh
the bad and vice versa?
You know, the very massive
ethical questions
that this show will pose.
We hope that you will
forge a better world,
a world that belongs to us again!
We'll see if Elliot and
everybody in fsociety...
are saving the world or destroying it.
Coming up, could
a small group of hackers
actually change the world overnight?
It's not a fantasy. It's
not science fiction.
Plus, we'll show you
what's in store for season two.
Amen, amen, amen!
This is "Mr. Robot dec0d3d."
Evil Corp, you have been owned.
We at fsociety will smile
as we watch you and your dark soul die.
USA Network's "Mr. Robot" is
groundbreaking television,
with cutting edge storylines,
detailed world building,
and uncanny parallels to current events.
Certainly a subject
matter that has become
more and more relevant as...
as the year has gone on.
Markets in Asia and Europe
are tumbling dramatically.
Numerous governments
in the European Union
are now in a free-for-all.
So this is what our evolution
Looks like: a simple program,
a worm that can make data unreadable.
Is that really all it
takes to kill the world?
But could the fsociety hack
portrayed in the show actually happen?
What would the fallout of
such a hack look like?
So we have plenty of companies
that kind of fall into that
"too big to fail" moniker.
It's kind of scary to think about
what the impact of a
destructive hack against them
could have on... on society.
You could wreck large
sectors of the power grid.
You could take down a whole bank.
You could do a lot of damage.
There are some key vulnerabilities
within our national infrastructure.
People could actually take
the entire Internet down.
A lone hacker really
can do immense damage,
or they can do immense good.
It's just all in the motivation.
I think it'd be possible.
Are there ramifications to that?
Of course.
Are there ramifications to that
that fsociety and Elliot
didn't even think of?
Definitely. And we're
gonna get into that
in season two.
There's gonna be, I bet,
a lot of people coming for them.
You know, law enforcement's
gonna be coming in season two.
It has to.
Season two of "Mr.
Robot" will
go deeper into this amazing world,
as the characters deal
with the repercussions of
the Evil Corp hack.
So we come back in season two
and the hack has gone through
and kind of destroyed the world.
The FBI announced today,
and we can confirm that
fsociety engaged in this attack.
Now that Elliot knows who Mr. Robot is,
it's very different from last year.
What he's trying to do at all costs
is to remove him from his world.
In the second season, the
story really picks up
and... and moves forward.
You know, we set up all the characters,
and now really in the second
season we're really kind of
letting all those characters run wild.
We're really going into
an ensemble sort of
version of the show.
We're in four or five different worlds
at the same time.
Just watching that
struggle and seeing people
at the end of their rope still persevere
and continue to fight,
even though their back's
against the wall.
In the second season,
all the characters have sort of evolved.
The world is very different.
Expect to be a little surprised
because we're going down a
very different direction
than the road we went
down in season one.
And Sam has got it really mapped out.
When I was reading these scripts,
and I was just saying, "Oh, my God."
There's these clues that you
kind of strand together.
I mean, we were like, Reddit people
discussing with each other
what we thought would happen.
He comes up with some crazy stuff.
I don't know what I'm supposed to do.
I'll tell you exactly
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna start listening to us.
The world is a better place
because of what we did, Elliot,
and you're gonna realize
that one way or another.
Now here's what I need you to do now.
So what has "Mr. Robot" taught us?
Working with the tech advisor
has got me to change the way
I conduct myself.
Someone actually asked me the other day
if I wanted to hack them, could I?
Unfortunately, the answer was no,
and I really wish it was yes.
I tend to be paranoid
about my own information.
My drives, my phone.
The microphone you have on
your computer can be accessed.
The camera, as much
as people don't think
it can be accessed, it can.
I tell other people to tape
the camera on their laptop.
Oh, yeah, put the piece
of tape on your laptop.
Absolutely a must.
I was literally actually about
to get tape and do that.
That's great.
I've infected my paranoia with everyone.
- sync and corrections by Mr. C -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -